♪ slow, dramatic music ♪
♪
Welcome to Iron Lake.
2,760.
On the surface,
Iron Lake may seem
like the idyllic snow globe town
Norman Rockwell
would jerk off to.
But I came here
because an overprivileged,
cis, white boy
named Matt Caldwell
went hunting
in the woods one day
and never came back.
So, of course, everyone
lost their goddamn minds.
Especially Matt's father,
local legend Kurt Caldwell,
who claims his son
is still alive.
But if that's true,
where is he?
What unfolded next,
murder fiends,
was more than
any true crime podcaster
could ever dream of.
Dark secrets lurk
beneath Iron Lake,
and the more I do the deep dive,
the more I come up with.
At this rate,
I may never have to leave.
You're listening
to Merry Fucking Kill.
And now, a word--
This is Chief Angela Bishop,
Iron Lake P.D.
I need you to put out
an APB on someone
who's been missing for 72 hours.
All right, what's
the name of the missing person?
Molly Park.
♪
Now I remember
why I picked this place.
So many good people.
Fred Jr, Pastor Brian.
Logan.
Teddy, Abraham.
Good folks.
All these people
working together to help me,
Mr. Serial Killer.
Make that
Mr. Serial Killer and son.
This fire is a sign.
If I'm going to teach
Harrison the Code,
it can't be here.
We need to talk.
Uh, sure thing.
You want to grab, uh,
- a coffee?
- No, we need to talk now.
Ah.
I just spoke to Gig.
There's strong evidence
that your fire was arson.
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
♪
Arson? Are you sure?
Yes. Yes, I'm sure.
'Cause Gig's been warning me
about that fire pit for--
Someone drenched your roof
with an accelerant,
most likely gasoline,
which makes this a crime scene.
Oh.
Why would someone do that?
Can you think of anyone
you crossed recently?
No one comes to mind.
It was probably those
Moose Creek douchebags.
Uh, a few of 'em tried
to jump me at the-at the
truck stop two nights ago.
- You were attacked?
- Yeah.
Did you get any names?
Uh, they were-they were friends
with that kid, Jeremy.
Uh, Zach or Scott
probably know who they are.
He truly is his father's son.
...I'm gonna need
physical descriptions
- Yo, Jimbo!
- and any other
details you can remember.
Anything here you want to keep?
Hey, thanks, Teddy.
This was my father's.
Jim!
Keep your phone on.
I'm gonna stay
and poke around a little more.
Heard about the fire.
Uh, took up a collection
to help out.
Aw, you shouldn't have.
You really shouldn't have.
We, uh, we wanted to get you
a little something special.
Thought you might
be able to use a new jacket.
Coach...
Hey, it's from all of us.
Yeah!
Gracias.
Para todo.
You guys are too nice
in this town.
Hey, it's your town, too.
There was a time
I would've given anything
to see him like this.
Aw, shit, he's gonna cry.
Happy. Embraced by friends.
Almost normal.
Okay, okay. Come on, come on.
Let's pack up the-the boxes
and put them in Jim's truck.
No, it's all good.
Harrison and I got it.
Thanks again.
You're too kind, really.
Takes a village.
So...
after last night,
we should probably figure out
where we want to live.
That makes sense.
Can't stay
at Angela's place forever.
Maybe somewhere warmer?
You mean away from Iron Lake?
That's what I'm thinking, yeah.
But-but I just got here.
I mean, I-I-I finally
feel like I fit in.
And you've done a great job,
but think about how good
a fresh start will feel.
What about Los Angeles?
It's kind of like Miami,
but without all that humidity.
It's 3,000 miles away
from my friends.
From Audrey.
I know it's hard,
but we can't be ourselves here.
We can't do what we do.
Come on.
So...
how does...
"what we do" work, exactly?
I mean, d-do we...
we see someone getting away
with murder, and...
uh, take care of them?
Something like that.
We'll research, make a list.
It's not hard to do
when you're in a big city.
And then, when our
Dark Passenger rises up,
we'll be ready.
Rises up?
Like during
your wrestling match,
when you broke that kid's arm.
Except, instead of hurting
someone innocent,
we bring justice
to someone who deserves it.
And save a lot
of innocent people.
Yeah.
Can we get a pool?
Yeah, we can definitely
get a pool.
♪ slow, sentimental music ♪
So, uh, when are you
gonna tell Angela?
'Cause I-I need to tell Audrey.
I'll let you know
when the time is right.
♪
Hey, could you follow up
on a few Moose Creek kids?
Harrison said they...
Harrison said they...?
Ange? Everything okay?
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
♪
All right.
- Thank you.
- Hey, you got a little...
♪ tense music ♪
Dogs... you know.
Hey, you.
I hope pasta's okay.
It seemed, I don't know, cozy.
Can't-can't go wrong with pasta,
but you got to do it right.
Would you guys mind
going to Gig's
for some crushed red pepper
and parmesan?
Yeah. You got it. Come on.
Oh, and, uh,
caramel fudge ice cream?
Yeah, get two.
We all deserve it.
All right.
Is my cabin still burned down?
Very.
Any clues, culprit-wise?
Yeah, I guess not.
Well, have some wine.
Sorry to say,
it's a little bit...
smoky.
You okay?
Hey. Don't worry about me.
I am the phoenix.
I rise from the ashes.
Hey, tell me what's going on--
Turn around! On your knees!
Hands on your head.
Wh-- You're taking the whole
role-playing thing
to the next level.
Shut the fuck up
and do what I say.
♪ ominous music ♪
♪
Okay.
What could she possibly know?
What the hell is this about?
'Cause there's at least
a few options.
Dexter Morgan,
you're under arrest
for the murder
of Matthew Stearn Caldwell.
Matt Caldwell's dead?
Get him the fuck
out of my house.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say--
Yes, okay, your chief already
told me to shut the fuck up.
♪ "A Wolf at the Door"
by Radiohead ♪
♪ Let me back, let me back ♪
♪ I promise to be good ♪
♪ Don't look in the mirror ♪
♪ At the face
you don't recognize ♪
♪ Help me, call the doctor,
put me inside ♪
♪ Put me inside ♪
♪ Put me inside,
put me inside, put me inside ♪
♪ I keep the wolf ♪
♪ From the door ♪
♪ But he calls me up, ooh ♪
Ange...
Can we just talk?
Oh, we'll be talking. A lot.
♪ And I'll never
see them again ♪
♪ If I squeal to the cops ♪
♪ No-no-no, no ♪
♪ No, no-no-no ♪
♪ No-no-no, no-no-no,
no-no-no-no ♪
♪ No-no-no-no ♪
♪ No-no-no-no, no-no-no ♪
♪ Someone else is gonna
come and clean it up ♪
♪ Born and raised for the job
someone always does ♪
♪ I wish you'd get up,
get over ♪
♪ Get up, get over,
turn your tape off ♪
♪ I keep the wolf
from the door ♪
♪ But he calls me up, calls me ♪
♪ On the phone,
tells me all the ways ♪
♪ That he's gonna mess me up ♪
♪ Steal all my children ♪
♪ If I don't pay the ransom ♪
♪ I'll never see them again ♪
♪ If I squeal to the cops ♪
♪ So I'm just gonna ♪
Dad? What's going on?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Take a seat, Harrison.
I'll talk to you in a bit.
Just grab a seat, guys.
Do I need a lawyer? 'Cause--
Up to you.
For the record,
please state your name.
Jim Lindsay.
State your goddamn name.
Dexter. Dexter Morgan.
Hello, Dexter Morgan.
Hello, Chief Bishop.
Where were you the day
Matt Caldwell went missing?
I was...
at my cabin, alone.
Okay.
We've determined
that this person
- is Matt Caldwell.
- Yeah.
You remember when I came in
and identified that
distinctive rifle for you?
Yes. You're a good citizen.
I try to be.
Do you really have
no sense of sarcasm?
No. - Yes.
I-- We never identified
the second person
out in the woods that morning.
What's interesting is
he has the same build as you,
the same rifle you own.
He even does that same
chin scratch thing you do.
Well, my body size is average,
- which means--
- I know what that means.
And dozens of people in
Iron Lake have that same rifle.
Hell, I personally sold
most of them.
And I don't really know
what you mean about...
...the chin scratch thing.
You know that Matt Caldwell
shattered his femur
in that boating accident
in Ohio?
I'd heard that. What about it?
These are
the type of screws and plate
used to repair
that sort of fracture.
Okay, and?
And I found them in my mailbox,
along with...
this note.
Come on, Ange,
you're better than this.
I found this...
in the ashes of your cabin.
♪ ominous music ♪
Remember when I said these
are the type of screws and plate
used on surgeries like Matt?
I was being oblique.
They're not just the type.
These are the actual screws
and plate used on Matt.
They've got serial numbers, so
I called
the Cleveland Clinic and--
And that's why we're here.
♪
And your working theory is...
You went for
your morning walk...
No, I was home all day,
except for work and--
...where you saw Matt
kill the white deer.
You two argued.
Not hard to do, considering
Matt was always an asshole.
Maybe he attacked you.
Maybe it was self-defense.
Or maybe you're jumping to
conclusions that aren't there.
And then Harrison
shows up out of nowhere...
...and you had to get rid
of Matt's body.
And what's your theory
on that one?
You burned it.
Smart.
Until it isn't.
'Cause here's the hitch.
Titanium...
...doesn't melt.
A fact I've become
painfully aware of.
I also have a theory.
You want to hear it,
or are you just gonna tell me
to shut the fuck up?
Kurt lied
about Matt being in New York.
And then he lied about Matt
being at that cabin of his.
And then Kurt stripped that
same cabin down to the studs
a day after your friend,
Molly and I were there.
So, it's not outside the realm
of good, logical theory
that Kurt killed Matt
for any number of
accidental or intentional reasons.
You yourself said,
"Matt was always an asshole."
Then he needed someone to frame.
Why not the boyfriend
of the chief of police
who just arrested
and humiliated him?
♪ tense music ♪
♪
Hell, Kurt probably
burned down my cabin
just so you'd find
that damn screw.
Don't you see? He set me up.
Ange...
he's trying to get back at you.
Look, you've been under
a ton of pressure lately.
And...
you just found your best
friend's body after so long.
You haven't even had a chance
to grieve for--
Don't you say her name!
Hey, hey.
Why don't we just give Jim--
Dexter-- some time
to gather his thoughts?
We want to keep
this interview clean,
so it stands up in court.
- He's fucking with us.
- Maybe.
But his story seems to be just
on this side of plausible to me,
which means it'll seem plausible
to a jury and the D.A.
You don't know
the full fucking context.
And if there is
a full fucking context,
you might want to fill me in.
I can't.
I got to be sure this time.
- Teddy.
- Chief?
Bring Kurt Caldwell in.
- You got it, boss.
- Anything on the Molly Park APB?
Nothing yet, but I forwarded
the line to my cell.
Okay. Harrison.
Logan will bring you in
to see your father.
Just... five minutes, okay?
Thanks, Ange-- Chief Bishop.
Audrey, you come with me.
Harrison.
Oh.
Sorry. Protocol.
Just hang tight.
- I'll give you some privacy.
- Thank you.
What the hell?
Angela thinks
I killed Matt Caldwell.
This has nothing
to do with Kurt. You're safe.
Hey, I've been in tougher spots.
I'll get out of this.
There's no way I'm leaving you.
I promise.
- Night, Logan.
- Good night, Esther.
Angela's got this... theory,
but it'll never hold up.
We'll be on the road
in a day or two.
Well, what am I supposed
to do till then?
Go find Tess at The Tavern.
She'll feed you
and give you a room.
- Okay.
- Come on, guys.
We'll get through this.
The world needs us.
I'll be waiting for you.
And I'll find you.
Hey.
Stay tough.
Turn around.
Hands behind your back.
You're a good man, Logan.
I hope you are, too,
for Harrison's sake.
I can't give you
all the details yet, but...
You know how Harrison told you
Jim wasn't his real name?
You said Harrison was high
and didn't mean it.
I didn't know it at the time,
but there's more to that story.
Like what?
What the hell is going on?
Honey,
I know this might be
hard to believe...
...but Jim is dangerous.
Dangerous?
Then why were you dating him?
Why'd you let him
into our house?
Sometimes people
aren't who you think they are.
Wait, Audz.
Go home.
Give Harrison some space.
Why? Is he dangerous too?
No.
Look...
I promise I will tell you
everything tomorrow.
Turn around.
Hands through the slot.
All right.
This is nuts.
It's really putting me
in touch with my fear
of Harrison growing up
without a father.
I know you've been there.
Go to the far side of the cell.
Tuna.
Huh. Some things never change.
I'm gonna go make sure
that Harrison is set up okay.
I'm not going anywhere.
And thank you.
Sons need their fathers.
Thanks for this.
Oh, you're doing me a favor.
Never fun eating alone.
I know this must be
really, really tough for you.
I'm not the one in jail.
I don't want to see Jim
go away, either.
Look, you got here around
the same time Matt disappeared.
Did you hear or-or see anything
that could help
exonerate your dad?
I-I wasn't in town yet, so I...
can't help.
Are you gonna finish your fries?
I should head back
to the station.
- Later, Coach.
- Yeah.
Thanks for stopping by.
Oh, and, uh,
try not to eat hamburgers
three meals a day.
I don't want you going up
too many weight classes
before wrestling starts
after New Year's.
♪ slow, somber music ♪
♪
Motherfucker.
♪ tense music ♪
♪
Batista.
This is Chief Angela Bishop.
We met at that conference
in New York.
Chief Bishop.
Uh...
I hope I didn't give you
the wrong impression.
You know,
I'm a happily married man.
This is a police matter.
How can I help?
We've had some deaths
in Iron Lake
that are very similar
to an old Miami Metro case.
Do you remember
the Bay Harbor Butcher?
Cristo.
That was a gruesome one.
I looked at the autopsy photos
on the police database.
- So, you've seen the, uh--
- The dismemberments.
The whole thing.
What can you tell me
about Sergeant Doakes?
I sat next to him
every day for ten years.
Do you believe that he did it?
I did at the time, but there
were a few other theories.
My, uh, my ex-wife...
My old captain actually thought
it was someone else
in the precinct.
Who?
Dexter Morgan,
but he died years ago.
Chief Bishop?
Check your e-mail.
Okay. Hold on.
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
♪
When was this taken?
Last month.
Madre de Dios.
Dexter Morgan is alive?
And is sitting in my jail cell.
Can I have your
old captain's name?
I'd like to speak with her.
She was...
she was murdered.
Oh, I'm... I'm so sorry.
Did you ever catch the killer?
-
- Batista?
Where are you?
I'll be there
first thing tomorrow
with everything I've got.
What's up, Teddy?
Kurt Caldwell's
beat feet out of here.
Front door unlocked,
safe empty, closets cleaned out.
And guess what?
His gas truck's here.
Emptied out.
Still smells like fresh gas.
Can you stay
at Kurt's overnight?
Just in case he shows up.
You got it, Chief.
♪ slow, dramatic music ♪
♪
Oh... geez.
Put that lying son of a bitch
back in my office.
You're not done for the night?
Oh, I'm just getting started.
You might actually get away with
the Matt Caldwell murder charge.
- Because I didn't do it.
- Oh, you did it, all right.
But I'm not entirely sure
my case will hold up enough
to convince the D.A.
and then the jury.
But hear this and know this.
I will stake my career,
my family,
my everything...
that you're a murderer.
I'm worried about you.
ketamine.
You picked up a healthy--
or unhealthy--
amount from Dr. Patel.
Yeah, I needed it
for Vincent van Goat.
You know he was sick.
Do you recognize this man?
Yeah, it's the piece of shit
who sold the drugs
that almost killed my son.
We...
ended up having
an unfortunate encounter.
About that encounter.
Miles O'Flynn
testified to me that,
"Just before he started pounding
on me, he poked me in the neck.
Like, with a needle
or something."
That was the exact same day
you picked up the ketamine
and several syringes
from Dr. Patel.
You think I drugged him?
I saw Logan question him
in this very station.
There's no way he was drugged.
Only because Logan and Teddy
showed up at Crystal Bar
before you could do it.
God, believe what you
want to believe.
You worked forensics in Miami.
You've seen
autopsy photos before.
Yes and yes.
Jasper Hodge.
Okay, I have no idea
where you're going with this.
It's called...
- A weal mark.
- ...a weal mark.
I heard he died
of an accidental
fentanyl overdose.
I can't say I'm sorry.
He also had ketamine
in his system.
And only in his system.
None was found anywhere
in his house or his car.
- Well, I can't speak to that.
- Well...
...then speak to this.
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪
Same weal marks.
Same drug showing up
in their tox report.
It's what we call a pattern.
And it's how I know that you,
Dexter Morgan...
...are the Bay Harbor Butcher.
The Bay Harbor Butcher
was Miami Metro Detective
Sergeant James Doakes.
Not everyone believes that.
Tomorrow you'll be arraigned
for the murder of Matt Caldwell.
I'm gonna do my best
to see that it sticks
and you get life without parole.
And then,
win or lose,
you're gonna have
a little reunion
with your old friend
Angel Batista.
Yeah.
I met him at that Cop-Con thing.
He's on his way up from Miami
as we speak.
We're gonna extradite
your ass to Florida
where you'll stand trial
as the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Florida.
A state with the motherfucking
death penalty.
Turn off the camera.
Why the hell would I do that?
I'll talk.
If you've got something to say,
just say it to the camera.
Listening.
What if I told you
you were right?
Well, then,
you'd be admitting to--
I'm not admitting anything.
I'm saying you were right
about Kurt Caldwell.
I can prove it.
Ange, you know in your heart
that Kurt killed Iris.
She was just his first.
He's been active for 25 years.
Very active.
What the hell are you
talking about?
Them.
Go to Kurt's cabin.
100 yards north
of the front door,
under a deadwood pile,
there's a hatch.
Open it, and you'll see
what real evil looks like.
I have dedicated
my entire life to this.
Yeah, and you've been met
with scorn and ridicule
at every turn because you've had
a gut feeling but no proof.
You go to that cabin,
and you'll finally have it.
Proof.
Fuck!
You turned off
the camera. What happened?
Put him back in his cell.
I've got to check something out.
- And that would be?
- Just fucking do it.
Harrison.
I-I came to get my stuff,
since it doesn't look like
we're gonna move in together.
Come in. Your stuff's upstairs.
I'm sorry.
I think this is all my fault.
How could this possibly
be your fault?
I told my Mom what you said
at the party.
If I had just kept
my mouth shut--
Th-This-this
isn't because of you.
Then what's going on?
No one will tell me
what's happening.
I know.
I just...
want this to be over.
For things to go back to normal.
Normal...
What's that?
Things certainly weren't normal
when you and I were on track
to becoming brother and sister.
So, you think this arrest means
our parents are breaking up?
My dad told me
to wait at The Inn.
But it's really nice to see you.
Well, my mom said
to give you space.
But I guess we don't always have
to do what our parents want.
Remember when you thought
not killing was the problem?
How's that going for you?
I can figure this out.
Angela's got her teeth in you.
She's never gonna let go.
You did.
I was your sister.
I trusted you.
I loved you.
Angela's pretty fucking far
from that right now.
Enough!
Enough.
Hey, Logan,
can I get some water?
Kind of been doing
a lot of talking today.
Yeah.
You talked Angela
right out of the station.
I'd give anything to know
what you said to her
when the camera was off.
I don't want to hurt you.
So, Angela was right about you.
She's a good cop
and so are you,
but this is inevitable.
So, just give me the keys.
Do it!
Don't be a hero, Logan.
I just need to get out
and see my son.
Good, good.
Good, good, good, good.
- Don't do that.
- Fuck you.
Damn it, Logan,
you should have listened to me.
♪ tense music ♪
♪
Yo, Coach. Is my dad okay?
It's me.
Wh-- Dad?
Where-where are you?
Come downstairs.
Meet me in front of the station.
Um, I'm at-I'm at Audrey's.
Okay, that's actually better.
Grab all your stuff.
My truck is in
Angela's driveway.
The key's in the cupholder.
Meet me where we found
the white deer.
I got it.
Sun's coming up. Go.
Now.
♪ ominous music ♪
♪
Oh!
Annie Kurtz?
Jennifer Nùñez.
Oh, my... oh, my God.
Shannon Luu.
Lily Kosnicki.
♪
♪ sinister music ♪
Molly.
♪
♪ intense, dramatic music ♪
Logan. Logan, are you there?
Logan, do you copy? Pick up.
That was faster than I expected.
Logan. We have multiple bodies.
Oh, fuck.
♪ tense music ♪
♪
Fuck!
'Sup, Chief?
Get me state troopers, CSI,
the coroners,
the motherfucking FBI.
I found something like 30 bodies
at the Caldwell property
on Stearn Road.
I need all the backup I can get
before this place turns into
a fucking media frenzy.
Holy shit. Got it. On it.
Wait, Teddy.
Have you heard from Logan
in the past hour?
No. I think he's still
at the station with Jim.
Fuck! Fuck!
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪
♪ slow, somber music ♪
Dad.
Grab your stuff
and leave the truck. Let's go.
Are you hurt?
No. I'm okay. Come on.
Whose blood is that?
I'll explain everything later.
We need to go.
Now.
Wait.
You called me
from Logan's phone.
Is that his blood?
There was no other way.
Is Coach dead?
Isn't the whole point
that you only kill people
that deserve it?
Coach Logan's a good person.
He wouldn't cooperate.
It's the only way I could
get back to you. Come on.
Look, we'll talk
about everything,
I promise,
but this is it.
We got to get out of here.
Yeah.
Don't get caught.
That's only a part of it.
Harrison--
Shut up.
You don't really care
about saving anybody, do you?
You're just feeding
this-this Dark Passenger.
I-It's not even a passenger.
It's fucking driving.
And you like it.
You slashing Ethan
and breaking
that wrestler's arm--
that's your own darkness.
You're just like me, buddy.
No.
I wanted to be like you...
so bad.
But m-my anger
isn't because I'm like you.
My-my anger is because of you.
Of-of course I'm angry.
You didn't just make
the decision to abandon me once.
You made that decision
every single day
you stayed away for ten years!
Well, I'm still your dad,
and I'm here now.
I'm right here.
Just come with me, buddy.
I can stop.
I can do it, with your help.
I'm not your fucking caretaker.
I'm your goddamn son.
I want...
I need to be with you.
You have to turn yourself in.
There's no other way.
If I do,
I get the death penalty.
Maybe you deserve it.
♪ somber music ♪
♪
Okay.
You don't have to come with me.
But I can't stay here.
Would my mom still be alive
if it weren't for you?
Would Aunt Deb still be alive?
And me--
would I be so fucked-up?
Open your eyes
and look at what you've done!
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪
You're right.
I don't...
I don't want to be right.
I...
I just-- I want to be normal.
♪ somber music ♪
♪
I'm sorry for everything
I've done to you.
You deserve better.
A better life.
A better father.
You have to take the safety off.
Just like I showed you.
♪ tense music ♪
♪
This is the only way out.
For both of us.
Now...
deep breath.
I've never really felt love.
Real love.
Until now.
♪ slow, somber music ♪
♪
You did good.
Drop the rifle! On your knees!
Hands where I can see them!
I'm-- I stopped--
He-he killed Coach Logan.
I know.
It's okay. You can get up.
Okay.
Take this.
Go through town,
just past the Truck Stop
is the entrance to I-86 west.
Go, and never come back here.
Harrison.
You need to do this now.
Uh, tell Audrey I said goodbye.
I can't.
Why?
Because I haven't seen you.
♪ slow, dramatic music ♪
♪
This is Chief Bishop.
I'm calling to report
an officer-involved shooting.
My dearest Hannah,
this is the most difficult
letter I'll ever write.
- You may have seen my name
among the casualties
of Hurricane Laura,
and I believe
that's for the best.
I'd give anything to see
you and Harrison again.
To see him smile.
To hold him.
I celebrate his birthday
in my heart.
♪ "I Should Live in Salt"
by The National ♪
He is and always will be
my phantom limb.
♪ Don't make me read your mind ♪
♪ You should know me ♪
♪ Better than that ♪
♪ It takes me too much time ♪
♪ You should know me ♪
♪ Better than that ♪
♪ You're not that much like me ♪
♪ You should know me ♪
♪ Better than that ♪
♪ We have different enemies ♪
♪ You should know me
better than that ♪
♪ I should leave it alone ♪
♪ But you're not right ♪
for his child to be happy.
To live and love without fear.
To share his gifts
with the world.
♪ I should leave it alone ♪
♪ But you're not right ♪
But we both know that,
with me around,
a normal life for Harrison
won't be possible.
♪ I should live in salt
for leaving you ♪
♪ Behind ♪
This is not an easy decision.
Sometimes I wish
the hurricane had taken me,
released me from the burden
of my own urges.
Instead, it showed me
that I have to bear them alone.
That's my fate.
So, unless Harrison starts
showing any dark tendencies,
I beg you...
♪ I should live in salt
for leaving you... ♪
Let me die
so my son can live.
♪ Behind ♪
♪