Previously on
New Blood...
I think this is human skin.
She bit her attacker.
What if Iris was just the first?
He's drifting further
and further toward Kurt.
What could possibly go wrong?
I like you. I thought
- you liked me, too.
- Last night,
you broke that kid's elbow.
Oh!
Kurt Caldwell, you're
under arrest for the murder
- of Iris Broussard.
- Who?
Give this to your dad.
- Stay away from my son.
- Titanium
doesn't melt.
He knows.
Jim showed up
at just the right time,
which is also weird.
I would totally do a deep dive.
But it's not like
he's hiding anything from you.
I'm fucked up,
and I always have been.
I remember everything.
Daddy will be home soon.
And I think about it
all the time, hurting people.
The stab wound
doesn't match the story
he told Angela.
Something's off.
This wound wasn't made
by a hunting knife.
Harrison brought his own weapon
to school that day.
He has my Dark Passenger.
What the fuck?!
- Hey, psycho!
- That's enough.
I have to tell Harrison
everything.
♪ On a hill far away ♪
♪ Stood an old rugged cross ♪
♪ The emblem ♪
♪ Of suffering and shame ♪
♪ And I love that old cross ♪
Hey, psycho!
♪ Where the dearest and best ♪
♪ For a world ♪
♪ Of lost sinners was slain ♪
♪ And I'll cherish
the old rugged cross ♪
♪ Cross ♪
♪ Till my trophies ♪
♪ At last I lay down... ♪
What you got now, ass wipe?
What the fuck?!
Psycho.
Fuck.
Oh. Oh.
Holy shit, man!
You fucking killed him!
Ah! No!
♪ And I'll cherish
the old rugged cross ♪
♪ Old rugged cross ♪
♪ Till my trophies ♪
♪ At last I lay down ♪
♪ Yes, I will cling ♪
♪ To the old rugged cross ♪
♪ And exchange it ♪
♪ Some day for a crown... ♪
♪
Who the hell is this guy?
Afternoon, Mr. Caldwell.
Hey, Elric,
could you turn the fucking
hillbilly music down a little?
Yeah. Sor-Sorry.
♪ The old ru... ♪
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Just checking in.
How's your job coming?
Oh, I got
your fish-and-game guy.
Oh, easy as pie.
You handling his son?
My son?
I'm handling everything.
I'll see you soon.
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
♪ up-tempo, dramatic music ♪
♪
Fuck.
Ah.
Fuck!
It almost fell, oh, my God.
Hello?
Hey, Harrison, I'm headed to
the Truck Stop. Are you there?
I thought you were in jail.
Oh, no, no, no.
That... We got that cleared up.
That was just
a misunderstanding.
Cool. Cool.
Y-Yeah, actually, I, um...
I-I'm not at the Truck Stop
right now. I had to leave
a little early, uh,
'cause my dad came by,
we had a huge fight.
What do you mean, a huge fight?
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Yeah, well,
it doesn't sound like it.
Your dad just doesn't let up,
does he?
Is he with you now?
N-No, I, um...
I don't know where he is.
Mm.
Uh, well, did he call you
to check to see if you're okay?
No.
Okay. Well, I'm sure he's just,
uh, tied up with something.
Hey, listen, buddy,
uh, where are you?
Um, I'm a-across the street
from the-the Christmas tree lot.
Okay, you stay right there,
all right?
I'm gonna come and pick you up.
I got a surprise for you.
♪ slow, ominous music ♪
I got to lose this guy,
get back to his truck
and find my son.
Hey. What's up?
It's Christmas Eve is what's up.
- Go home.
Yeah. I'm...
I'm headed out soon.
- You good?
- I will be.
Well, you know,
if you ever, uh,
want to grab a drink
or anything...
...I'm sure that Jim would love
to hear from you.
Did you hear that we-we had
drinks the other night?
- I didn't.
- You know, he acts
all easy breezy,
but underneath, he's...
He cares a lot
about you and Harrison.
I mean, look at how
upset he got
after his kid almost OD'd.
Nearly killed that drug dealer.
What are you talking about?
Uh, that's right.
You were, um...
You were in New York.
Well, we went to Crystal Bar
to arrest the drug dealer,
Miles O'Flynn.
Jim had already found the guy
and was, uh,
beating the shit out of him.
- How did you not tell me this?
- Oh, I meant to. I just...
Okay, look,
I didn't want it to look like
I was talking shit
about your boyfriend.
Uh, his anger got
the best of him.
If-if it was my kid, I probably
would have reacted the same way.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I-I-I wasn't trying to,
you know,
make you upset or anything. I--
Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
It's... it's been a tough week.
♪ eerie, dramatic music ♪
♪
I really hate it
when I'm the one who's bleeding.
♪ slow, suspenseful music ♪
♪
Your son's blood.
It's all on your hands.
Goddamn save him.
I'm working on it.
That's it. I guarantee
it'll make you feel dyno-mite.
- Shit. No, I wasn't doing shit!
- Hey! Hey, hey!
You've got some time to talk.
Fucking bullshit! I was just
- drinking a beer, man.
- Relax, Miles.
I'm not gonna hurt you
or bust you.
I'm here to ask you about your
encounter with Jim Lindsay.
Who?
He was the guy
who did that to your face.
Oh. That guy. Fucking lunatic.
Yeah. I'm still thinking
about pressing charges.
Do you want
to tell me what went down?
This isn't like a trick
or something, right?
Like, you're not trying
to entrap me?
Okay?
'Cause I'm not fucking stupid.
No? Well, you help me out,
I'll return the favor.
Okay. All right.
So, I was at the bar,
having a drink,
when that, uh, Jim dude,
or whatever his name is,
comes over to me,
all friendly and shit.
- Friendly?
- Yeah. He asks me
if I could... do him a favor.
Heard you might know
where to get some blues.
Follow me outside.
He asked you for drugs?
Your words, not mine.
Anyway, so he gets me outside
over by the dumpsters.
So I could...
So you could do him that favor?
Right. Except out of nowhere,
he fucking jumped me.
He just started attacking you
with no provocation?
Yeah, just started
swinging at me.
And look, okay,
this is gonna sound crazy,
but before he started
pounding on me,
he poked me in the neck, with,
like, a needle or some shit.
- A needle?
- Yeah, and so, I was like,
"What the fuck?" And I look up,
and I see the police rolling up,
and I'm like,
what the actual fuck?
And that's when he started
throwing fists, man.
- Wait. Wait.
- He's got fast hands, yo.
He starts punching you
after the cops show up?
Yeah, man. Yeah, just right
as they rolled up.
And the thing he poked you with,
you're sure it was a needle?
Well, I-I didn't really
get a good look at it, okay?
It all happened so fast,
but, like, I mean, look.
I still got the fucking mark.
Check it.
Kurt said I had
to bring you in alive.
You know what?
He'll just have to understand.
Right?
I mean, you know, shit.
I think the school's closed for,
you know, Christmas break.
Yeah, well, they haven't
changed the locks
since I was Matt's wrestling
coach, so...
What about security cameras?
Oh, you mean
for our precious children?
No, those are reserved
for tracking white deer
because that's what's important, right?
Sometimes it feels good to be bad.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
Besides, what are they gonna
do-- arrest me? Again?
Fucking snow.
Even a three-year-old
could track me.
Come on, big man,
head on down that creek
so I can get back to my son.
First perfect game
- in school history.
- That's Matt?
Yeah. He was about your age.
Ah, I used to go
to every one of his games.
That's what I loved most
about being a dad.
Whoa. He lettered
in three sports?
Yeah. He was...
he was special.
Well, how's he doing?
Have you talked to him lately?
Actually...
I haven't, you know.
Uh, we never really
communicated very well.
Not like you and me.
Oh.
Does that mean he's not
coming home for Christmas?
Uh... you know,
with all the search party,
I think he's afraid
to show his face around here.
That's too bad.
People are pretty forgiving.
Especially during the holidays.
Not everyone.
Hey, let's go
have some fun, huh? Come on.
Oldest trick
in the goddamn book.
You want to play games?
I can do this all fucking day.
You might have
all day, but I don't.
- Shit. This is great.
Yeah. Right?
Small towns love them
some sport, huh?
I mean, what else
we gonna do, right?
Okay.
Uh, let's see...
That one...
All right.
- Put that ball right in here.
- All right.
All right, wait for me
to get down there.
Okay.
All right, anytime.
Whoa!
Wow. Matt's got nothing
on you, huh?
Yeah, well, I led
the Mountain League
in batting my senior year.
Taught him everything...
he knows.
All right, that's enough.
Let's turn this thing off before
I hurt myself showing off.
You ever play?
- What, Jim never taught you?
- No.
All right.
Let's see what you got.
Summer camp.
Perfect place for
a serial killer
to make his stand.
All right. Batter up!
Sorry.
It's okay, you don't have
to apologize.
Okay. Here you go.
It's all right.
You just weren't taught right.
Y-You're swinging with
your wrists, all right?
Good instincts,
but you've got to use
your whole body, right?
You've got to step
with your legs.
Swing. Whole body.
There you go. Good.
One more time.
Step. Whole body.
All right, now, this time,
step, whole body,
snap your wrists. Ready?
Step, whole body, snap!
There you go. There.
You're not afraid,
are you?
- No.
- Good.
Now...
Ready?
Okay. Just... relax.
Keep your head down.
Eye on the ball, all right?
-♪ gentle music ♪
- Ready?
♪
Hey, attaboy!
Attaboy. All right.
Good, good, good.
Now, step into it.
Oh!
There we go.
- Whew! Good God!
This is getting
too easy for you.
You know what?
Let's try a curve ball.
See how you handle that.
All right. Here we go.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm-I'm good.
All right.
Okay.
Turn it back on.
Sorry. I'm not the guy
you're looking for.
Put another one in.
And my own dad thinks I'm what?
A liar? An animal?
Again.
Again!
You are one tough fucking kid.
So, you ever had venison?
No, I-- No, I've never had it.
Really? You mean the whole time
you've been here in Iron Lake,
Jim hasn't cooked you up
some venison?
Nope.
Oh. I don't know what the hell
he's waiting for.
Come on, we're gonna rectify
that situation right now.
All right. Let's go.
I also see some
quality Scotch
in your future.
♪ ominous music ♪
I thought we were
headed to your place.
We are. I have a cabin
out this way.
Oh, cool.
Yeah. I do all my hunting
out here.
It's where I keep my venison.
It's nice, you know.
To have a place you can go
to get away, be yourself.
Yeah.
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪
Hope he's as drawn
to blood as I am.
♪
You said you had all day.
Well, I've got news for you.
The night is mine.
What's going on?
Everything okay?
Yeah. It's just...
You know what?
You were right.
I pushed everything aside
to deal with Iris.
I want to close out
all our files.
- Now?
- Yeah, I keep thinking about
that story you told me
about the opioid bust.
You mind bringing me up to speed
on that case?
Okay, um,
once we arrested Miles,
I got him to snitch on
his supplier.
Piece of shit
named Jasper Hodge.
I coordinated with the Staties
to make the arrest,
- but we got there too late.
- It was too late?
Yeah. When we went
to make the arrest,
he was already dead.
Accidentally OD'd
on his own product
while he was pressing pills.
How long had he been dead
when you found him?
About an hour before
we got there.
So... maybe Miles
tipped Jasper off
that the police were coming?
Maybe he OD'd because
he didn't want to spend
- all those years in prison?
- I don't think so.
I mean, when I brought Miles
and Jim into the station,
Miles gave up Jasper quick.
But we held Miles for 24 hours,
and Jasper was dead in ten.
How long did you keep Jim
in custody?
No more than an hour. I mean,
I wasn't trying to punish him.
I just wanted to make sure
he cooled off.
♪ ominous music ♪
♪
Stupid motherfucker took
a knife to a gun fight.
All right.
Yeah. Okay.
♪ intense music ♪
♪
Christ! Who the hell are you?
Where does Kurt have my son?
Fuck you!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I think Kurt's got him
up in his cabin on Stern road.
That's where I was to bring you.
That's all I know.
I was just doing my job.
No-Nothing personal.
We're talking about my son.
There's nothing more personal
than that.
Do you see this often?
Fentanyl overdose?
Are you kidding?
- By the guy making the pills.
- Eh, it happens.
He had, um,
ketamine in his system, too.
That could explain it.
- Was it lethal drug interaction?
- No.
A party drug.
Probably took it to mellow out.
- Made him sloppy.
- So, there's nothing to suggest
that Jasper's death was
anything other
than an accidental overdose?
Well, not unless
someone put a gun to his head
and made him snort a line.
Just want to check
one more thing.
- Fucking faster, Dex!
- I'm going as fast as I can.
- Text him. Warn him.
- It's risky.
- You have to let him know.
- I don't want to tip off Kurt.
This is the good stuff.
This is what they call
single malt Scotch whisky.
Best there is.
Only kind I drink.
- Thank you.
- Go ahead. Give it a shot.
- Hmm?
Ooh. That kind of tastes
like a Band-Aid.
You want to put
some ice on that?
No, I'm good.
Mm.
Got to stop doing that
to yourself, kid.
I mean, look, I get it.
I-I used to do stuff like that
when I was your age.
But the sooner you stop
punishing yourself
for whatever you think
is wrong with you...
Look, all I'm trying
to say is that
you are who you are.
Find what gives you joy,
and you do that thing.
No apologies.
Whatever it is that brings you
pleasure in this world.
How do you...
H-How do you do that?
You just... take the leap.
Well, I have
worked up quite an appetite.
How about you?
Starving.
Whoo! This is gonna be tasty.
Uh, hey, I'm-I'm getting
a little cold.
Where's the firewood
for the stove?
Um, it's around the side of
the house. I'll get it.
Oh, no, no, no. I got it.
Come on, Harrison.
Come on. Come on.
You good?
Yeah.
You know, if it's getting late
and you need to be home,
I'm happy to give you a ride.
No. No way.
I wouldn't want to miss out
on all the venison.
Yeah, it's smelling
pretty tasty in there.
I'm glad we're doing this, kid.
Me, too.
All right. Hurry up.
Shit.
So I'm trying to make weight.
And I-- you know. I start
wearing a-a garbage bag, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- And then go for a run.
I'm drenched in sweat,
I got terrible BO,
and I'm wearing
a frigging Hefty bag.
- Mm.
- I run around the corner,
and there she is,
- walking her dog.
- Oh, man.
I had been gearing up
to ask her to the Spring Dance
all week,
but, you know, at school,
there's always people around,
and I... I don't know.
I just kept pussying out.
- I get it.
- So, this time,
I say, "Okay, forget about it."
I'm-I'm gonna take my shot.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna ask her.
Right there, right then.
What'd she say?
Well, she looked me
up and down,
like I had just escaped
from a mental ward, and said,
"Do I look like I date
white trash?"
Just laid me out.
But you probably don't have
that problem.
You're going out with the police
chief's daughter, right?
Uh, I don't know.
After that last wrestling match,
I-I think she looks at me like
I just escaped a mental ward.
Well, you know, I guess some
people are just never
gonna understand guys
like you and me.
You know what I say?
Fuck 'em.
- Yeah.
- Fuck 'em!
Attaboy.
Ah.
So... so-so what happened
with you going to jail?
W-What was that about?
Well, it was...
just a little mix-up
with some DNA.
Well, it turns out
that my dad
murdered a teenage girl
in Iron Lake 25 years ago.
- Oh, shit.
- Yeah.
He was a really messed up guy.
Wasn't easy growing up being
his son, I can tell you that.
And I guess, you know,
since I spent the night
in jail because of him,
it still isn't easy.
Eh, you know.
Sometimes a kid
just ends up suffering
for the...
choices of his father.
So, hey, why did the dad that
abandoned you for ten years
end up getting in a fight
with you at my truck stop?
Oh, I-I don't even know
if it was a fight
as much it was just me
being pissed at him
- all the time.
- Ah.
I just feel like I keep wanting
something from him that...
What? What do you want, kid?
I don't know. I...
When I came here,
I wanted answers.
A-And now, as much as I...
fucking hate to say it...
I-I think I was also
looking for, you know...
Connection. Real connection
with your dad. Hmm?
Yeah.
But I-I think he knew.
Even when I was five,
I think, I think he knew
how different we were.
Yo, this is Harrison. Leave a
message and I'll hit you back.
Well, w-we don't get
each other on, like,
a-a normal,
father-son level.
I-I feel like he's always
holding something back from me,
or... I don't know.
Whatever blood-bond most fathers
have with their kids,
it's-it's not there.
Listen to me. You cannot
blame yourself for that.
That is on him.
Yeah.
Maybe it's his
childhood abandonment shit.
Maybe it's mine.
E-Either way,
I got my answer.
If you were my son,
I would never have
walked out on you.
Ever.
- Tha-Thank you for saying that.
- I mean it.
- Ah, damn.
- What's up?
Uh...
Just something I have to
take care of.
Okay. I'll be right back.
♪ intense music ♪
W-What are you doing?
Wish it could've worked out
differently.
But I don't have a choice, son.
Sins of the father.
It's a fucked-up world
out there.
- I-I don't...
- Get up.
Get out.
What-what-what,
did I say something wrong?
Did I do something?
I-I didn't mean to do anything.
J-Just tell me what I did
and I'll make it right.
I'm-I'm-I'm sorry.
I don't know what I did.
Please, Kurt.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm sorry.
Run.
Run!
Come on!
Get him out of the car!
- I want him to see this.
Come on!
♪ dramatic music ♪
Oh, shit.
Harrison!
♪ gentle music ♪
- Are you okay?
- I'm-I'm not hurt.
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪
Where'd he go?
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
♪ contemplative music ♪
♪
Ketamine...
How did you know we were there?
D-Did you know Kurt was...
What's-what's going on?
There's so much
I need to tell you.
I should've way before
it got to this.
You need to know.
♪ gentle music ♪
What?
♪
Before anything else,
you need to know
that you never have to feel
alone with your dark...
thoughts again.
You were probably
drawn to Kurt because
he seemed to understand you,
but I...
...I was born in blood,
just like you.
I had the same violent urges
when I was your age.
Like you, I didn't know
how to deal with them.
But my dad taught me a code.
A way to channel those urges.
I'm gonna tell you everything.
This is all I had to do.
This is all he ever wanted.
Maybe, if I'm being honest...
maybe this is all
I ever wanted, too.
♪ mysterious music ♪
♪