Previously on
New Blood...
If he wasn't your boyfriend,
I would totally do a deep dive.
Hey, Miles.
I'm here to ask you
about your encounter
with Jim Lindsay.
He fucking jumped me.
He poked me in the neck with,
like, a needle or some shit.
[Molly] I mean, I got
some really creepy vibes
from Kurt.
It's the kind that I tell
my listeners to run away from
as fast as they can.
I think about it all the time.
Hurting people.
You've always known.
That's why you left.
When I came here,
I-I wanted answers.
Whoa!
[Harrison] I think I was
also looking for...
Real connection with your dad.
Whatever blood bond
most fathers have
with their kids,
it's...
...it's not there.
Where does Kurt have my son?
Up at his cabin on Stearn Road.
Nothing personal.
We're talking about my son.
There's nothing more personal
than that.
Run.
Run!
Harrison!
What's going on?
There's so much
I need to tell you.
I should've way before
it got to this.
You have everything?
Did you guys have fun?
It's a scary world out there.
Guilty people slip
through the cracks
of the justice system every day.
Ooh!
Oh! Wiggles loves it!
ominous music
And there he is,
Jeremiah the giraffe,
for the birthday girl. Mwah!
Now, can I have everybody say,
"Happy Birthday, Sam!"
Happy Birthday, Sam!
Oh, and let me get a picture
of the birthday girl.
-Okay.
And all of you...
Murderers. Rapists. Predators.
Monsters who walk among us,
and we never even know.
Counting on the justice system
to discover these predators
and effectively deal with them
is not an option.
Not for me.
I don't follow society's rules.
But that doesn't mean
there aren't rules
I have to follow
when the Dark Passenger calls.
Wait.
What-What's the Dark Passenger?
It's the name I gave the...
-calling that I have.
Hey.
Careful.
Always there,
riding alongside me.
Giving me...
A lot of bad ideas.
Sometimes...
...I have the urge
to hurt people.
An urge too strong to ignore.
The Dark Passenger.
That sounds right.
W-Why...
...why-why are we like this?
We both saw our mothers murdered
when we were young.
You, too?
I-I've always felt so alone.
I thought no one
could understand me.
I-I mean, if I, if I
talked about this shit
with anyone...
They'd lock you up.
When your grandfather Harry
found out what I was...
I thought he'd send me
to an institution.
But instead...
he gave me the Code.
It's a rigid process.
Once someone is identified
as worthy of the Code,
100% proof of their crimes
must be found.
gentle, dramatic music
It's not always easy to find.
Secrets are secret for a reason.
As a cop, Harry saw too many
criminals get arrested
and escape the law.
Then hurt innocent people
over and over.
He taught me how to make sure
they never hurt anyone
ever again.
So...
when did your dad
decide to teach you
this Code?
I was about your age
when I started exhibiting
violent tendencies.
Harry kept it a secret
from the rest of the family.
Fucking-A he did.
Well, they would've been
afraid of you.
But I would never hurt family.
Harry gave me the Code
as a way to channel
the Dark Passenger.
To use it for good.
F-For good?
And a way forward in life.
Ooh!
You like... the caramel?
Oh!
Oh.
Oh...
What the fuck?
[Dexter] Once I have proof
of their crimes,
the Code allows me to stop them
from hurting others.
I do what the law failed to do.
I fix things.
Hello.
You kidnapped him?
I did.
Wiggles was a threat.
He would've
tortured and killed that kid.
Hey. That's enough.
Well, then what?
So...
I prepare a place to...
...confront these bad people.
gentle, dramatic music
I have to be very neat
because the world will never
understand what I do.
I always show them
their victims.
It's important
that they open their eyes
and look at what they've done.
You abso-fucking-lutely
cannot tell Harrison
about your sick-ass ritual.
What the hell is this?
What's going on?
They always say
some shit like that.
Stop clowning around, Wiggles.
You know exactly
what's going on.
You...
remember... them all.
You tell Harrison that you kill
people, there's no going back.
So, doing that...
confronting him...
that-that made him stop?
Scaring him like that?
Fine.
I won't tell him.
Yes. He never hurt anyone again.
So, you're-you're kind of like
Batman or something.
I like Dark Defender.
And that...
that makes the Dark Passenger
not push so hard?
This is a lot.
It's not every day
you're nearly murdered
and then find out this.
Is Kurt gonna come after us?
If I were him,
I'd be 500 miles away by now.
It's getting late.
You should get some sleep.
Okay.
Good night, Dad.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, yeah.
You, too.
[Dexter] I still have
one more gift to wrap
in plastic.
"It's The Most Wonderful Time
Of The Year" by Andy Williams
It's the most wonderful time
Of the year - Ding, dong, ding, dong
With the kids jingle belling
And everyone telling you
Be of good cheer - Ah, ah, ah
It's the most wonderful time
Of the year - Ding, dong, ding, dong
It's the hap-happiest
Season of all - Ding, dong...
With those holiday greetings
And gay happy meetings
When friends come to call - Ah, ah, ah
It's the hap-happiest season
Of all
There'll be parties
for hosting, marshmallows...
Once you take care
of old fuckbilly here,
Harrison's gonna have
more questions.
And when he asks, I'll answer.
You ever think about
how screwed up it is
you watched your mom get chopped
up in a shipping container,
and now you do the same shit
to your victims?
And Harrison dealt
with his trauma
by arming himself
with a straight razor,
the same weapon...
used to kill his mother.
What can I say?
We are what we are.
It's the most
Wonderful time
Oh, the most...
At least Elric's frozen,
no bloody mess.
...of the year
ominous music
A Stratocaster?
Oh, my God. It's beautiful.
Merry Christmas, sweetheart.
Gonoohgwa'.
-I love you, too.
Morning.
I-Is this for me?
It is Christmas.
Harrison seems to be all right.
Maybe the truth
hasn't ruined anything.
-Is that for me, too?
-Only one way to find out.
Wow.
Do you use this when, you know,
you know, you go after bad guys?
No. Never. Guns are...
loud, messy.
Plus I'm not a very good shot.
This is all about blending in.
All the guys at school
have guns.
Exactly.
Can we go outside and shoot it?
Here.
-There you go.
-Yeah.
Harry always said to, uh,
breathe out before you shoot,
and keep the butt up tight...
here, like this.
It'll save you from bruising.
-What is...
-Oh, you got to...
take the safety off.
-There.
-Okay.
Like that. There you go.
-You're ready to go.
-Okay. You need to--
-I got it.
Look at you.
That's better
than I've ever been.
He's a natural.
So, I was, I was thinking
about Kurt last night.
Oh?
Was he trying to kill me because
you were going after him,
like-like with Wiggles?
Kurt has been killing innocent
women for the last 25 years.
Wait, what? Wh...
Kurt's a serial killer?
H-How long have you known this?
I just found out.
Why didn't, why didn't you
tell Angela?
I don't have any proof.
Not yet.
Plus Kurt's already
been arrested
for one murder.
-And he got away with it.
-Yup.
Wh-What if I testified
that he tried to shoot me?
That-That's
attempted murder, right?
And then Angela starts to ask
a lot of questions
about what I was doing
out on his property.
Questions I can't answer.
Vigilante shit.
Yeah.
But I do have a plan
to make sure Kurt
can't hurt anyone else.
Ask me what the plan is.
Ask me if you can help.
Shit, I-I forgot.
I, um, I made you a gift.
One second.
I know it's not much.
It's kind of how I remember her.
Thank you. I love it.
You got any more, uh,
got any more bottles somewhere?
I do, but I think
it's time for us
to go exchange presents
with Angela and Audrey.
Yeah. Yeah, right.
Oh, I do have
one other gift for you.
It's, uh, part of the whole...
blending in thing.
It's kind of a tradition
I've been doing.
Thank you.
Oh, look at this.
You're kidding.
I have one, too.
-Ho ho ho.
Oh. Wow.
Those are-are very, very,
-very...
-Very Christmas-y.
Uh, gift from Dad.
Tradition.
Your dad's like the king
of Christmas sweaters.
Guess that makes you the prince?
Uh, yeah, I-I guess so.
-Want to put these by the tree?
-Mm-hmm.
Merry, happy Christmas, babe.
-Mm.
Back at you.
How was your night?
Uh, was uneventful.
How was yours?
Uh, once the presents were
wrapped, I slept like a baby.
Wonderful.
"Rockin' Around the
Christmas Tree" by Brenda Lee
Rockin' around
the Christmas tree...
I present to you...
-monkey bread.
Mistletoe hung
Where you can see
every couple...
Oh.
Oh, merry Christmas to me.
It's delicious.
You seem... different.
Like happy.
I think I...
I don't know...
found a way to let go
of my anger.
Best Christmas gift ever.
We might have to figure out
what to do
if our kids become an item.
Voices singing
let's be jolly...
Ah, food.
-My favorite part of Christmas.
Rockin' around
Nice.
Very nice.
Go Hawks.
-Your turn.
Look at you,
feeding my addiction.
Oh, my God.
We'll have to get one
for you next year, huh?
I'm-I'm good with just this one.
Uh...
Uh, you'll have to remember,
uh, my dad gets a discount
-at a certain store.
Mm.
Aren't a lot of options
in the Iron Lake.
I love it.
Nó'yeh,
what do you think?
-It's lovely.
It's your turn. Open your gift.
Huh.
The Police Handbook on
Searches, Seizures and Arrests.
My father Harry had
a lot of books like that
and used them a lot.
Saw you didn't have it
in your library, so...
That's very thoughtful.
And so romantic, Jim.
-Yeah.
A successful Christmas.
Surrounded by family.
Who could that be?
Merry Christmas, Chief.
Kurt, what are you doing here?
Mind if I come in?
Uh...
I just brought you
a little gift,
show you that there's
no hard feelings.
Oh. Thanks, Kurt.
Jim.
Harrison.
If I'd known you guys
were gonna be here,
I would've brought you two
a little something as well.
Ah.
I'm just jealous that Jimbo here
gets to spend the holidays
with his son.
Yeah, I hear you.
It certainly would be
a tough Christmas
without Harrison by my side.
Would've ruined
the whole holiday.
Yeah. Well, peace be with you.
And also with you.
Merry Christmas
to you, too, kiddo.
Hope to see you around.
Well, hey, enjoy
the peppermint bark.
Had it shipped in from the city.
It's the best around.
Well, Ange,
Harrison and I got to go.
What? No.
Uh, yeah.
Dad and I had
plans to go...
um, shooting.
Yeah, I got Harrison
a rifle for Christmas.
He wants to try it out.
So, love you.
See you tonight.
-Yeah.
I'll...
I'll talk to you later.
I'll see you.
That was weird, right?
It's his first Christmas
with his son in a long time.
It's not that weird.
suspenseful music
He didn't run.
Do you think
he's sticking around
-to finish what he started?
What-what if he goes
after Audrey or something?
Just get in the truck.
I know what I want to do.
But I'm not alone in this.
What if we did
what you did with Wiggles?
We'd have to find proof first.
Like the pictures
the clown had of the kids?
Yeah. Killers like Kurt
usually keep some kind
of trophy, a memento,
to remember what
they did to their victims.
It could be anything,
piece of clothing,
jewelry, photo.
They know it could
get them caught,
but they can't help themselves.
You think Kurt does that?
And I think he keeps them
on his property,
near the cabin.
Salena?
Merry Christmas, Angela.
Everything all right?
Yeah, just, the job doesn't pay
attention to the holidays,
but I do come bearing gifts.
Just doing a little follow-up
on a case, um...
Think you could open the books
on purchases of ketamine?
In the last month or so?
Oh... Um...
Yup. I've got three
in last month.
Mrs. Gross for her sheep.
Um, Al Chung for his cows,
and Mr. Harris
for his 37 cats.
Great.
Oh, wait.
Your boyfriend Jim.
Said he needed it for his goat,
Vincent van Goat.
That's a cute name.
Thanks.
dramatic music
Yo, Kurt.
Fuck you
and thanks for the drone.
Ah, the gift
that keeps on giving.
People don't just vanish.
I know, I've tried.
I have to tell you something.
You were right...
about what I did.
With Ethan.
I mean, shit, I-I-I set
the whole thing up
so that I could
get away with it.
Maybe even look like a hero.
How did you know?
Blood spatter analysis.
From my Homicide days.
I'm-I'm sorry
I-I treated you like shit
when you knew the truth.
I was...
I was just afraid.
Wh-Why didn't you tell me
all this back then?
I wanted to.
But I needed to try out
everything else first.
Therapy.
That's why you were
so closed off.
I knew you were
hiding something.
I've been thinking
about Wiggles.
About the end.
You said you
made sure he didn't hurt
anyone else again.
I mean, scaring the shit
out of him,
even hurting him.
I mean, that-that
doesn't feel...
I don't know...
like justice.
And what would...
justice feel like to you?
When I was 12 years old,
I started having fantasies about
hunting down the Trinity Killer.
You know he just
up and disappeared?
I wanted to kill him.
With his own razor.
I wanted to do it slowly.
I understand.
Wait. Hold it right there.
That's... strange.
See that? Can you go in closer?
That's right where
Kurt disappeared.
Holy shit. That's big.
That could be where he kills.
Maybe where he keeps
his trophies.
I-Is that a vent?
-Let's go.
-Wait.
don't get caught.
We wait until dark.
Come back tonight
and check it out.
Okay.
Outside of Harold Shipman
or Luis Garavito,
the Bay Harbor Butcher
was one of the most prolific
serial killers of all time.
He's one of the most
sick-ass, decapitating,
dismembering murderers
out there.
And by the end of this podcast,
I'm gonna challenge everything
you may think you know about
who... he... was.
Hey.
Hey, yourself.
Look,
I hope it doesn't bum you
and Audrey out too much,
but would it be okay if
Harrison and I don't
come over tonight?
Me and the kid have been
really bonding.
That's really great.
Uh, it's no problem.
Yeah, we're gonna go
on a night hike
and check out that blood moon
that's been happening.
That's fine. Have fun.
Yeah. Merry Christmas. Love you.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
As I walk along
I wonder
A-what went wrong
with our love
A love that was so strong
And as I still walk on
- I think of
The things we've done
Together, while our hearts
Were young
This is too much.
Is it?
He fantasized
about killing Trinity.
Who fucking didn't?
He admitted to wanting
to kill Ethan.
-He's just like me.
-Then cut it short
at finding the psycho's
trophies. That's enough.
You don't have to do
any of this with him.
I'm not forcing
any ideas on Harrison.
I want to help him,
just like Harry helped me.
There were fucking
alternatives, Dexter.
Therapy! Institutionalization!
Prison might have been better
in the long run.
You think prison
would be better?!
Whose side are you on?
Harrison was born in blood.
His Dark Passenger
pushes him to hurt others.
This path, it's the only way.
And you fucking love it.
His victims
were usually criminals
who'd gotten away with it.
That's some Batman-level
vigilante shit.
And it's why
Miami Metro Homicide
came to believe the Butcher
was one of their own.
Sergeant James Doakes.
But... what if they were wrong?
Well, maybe the police didn't
want to keep investigating
the biggest case
in Miami Metro history,
but I fucking do.
Because if I'm right,
the Bay Harbor Butcher
could still be out there.
Still feeling all butcher-y.
Still a threat.
And...
Oh, my God. You freaked me out.
-You freaked me out.
-Sorry.
-Ooh, Merry Fucking Kill.
BHB. Bad guy killer.
Chops them up,
dumps them in the ocean.
What do you think?
Did they get the wrong guy?
I don't know.
But if she's right,
I'd be scared shitless
to put it out there so publicly.
She certainly is brave.
Times like this,
I'm glad we live in the sticks,
away from monsters like that.
- Gonoohgwa', Mom.
-I love you, too, sweetheart.
Sleep tight.
Hi, hi. You've reached
my merry fucking voice mail.
When the beep beeps,
leave a message.
"War" by Idles
Wa-ching
That's the sound
of the sword going in
Merry Christmas, Jimbo.
Clack, clack,
clack-a-clang, clang
That's the sound of the gun
going bang, bang
Tukka-tuk, tuk, tuk,
tuk-tukka
That's the sound
of the drone button pusher
Shh, shh, shh
That's the sound
of the children tooker
This means war
Anti-war
War
Come on.
Good. Fucker's not home.
This is it.
Yup.
There's-there's definitely
something under here.
How does he get in?
Come see.
Teach me how to do that?
You can stay up here
and stand watch.
I have to see this.
Okay.
Follow me.
Wait, wait, wait.
What is that?
It's a camera.
Don't worry.
It's time for Kurt to know
that all his secrets are out.
Fuck.
Goddamn it. God...
Damn it.
hypnotic music
intense, suspenseful music
These... th-these are...
His trophies.
Merry. Fucking. Kill.
He's been getting away
with this... for years.
So many women... dead.
Until you found him.
You killed Wiggles, didn't you?
Please don't.
I did.
And I took care
of Arthur Mitchell, too.
Trinity.
I killed him for what he did
to your mother.
For what he did
to so many others.
This motherfucker
needs to die, too.
[Angela] So, when did Molly Park
check out?
The 23rd.
Couple days before Christmas,
so, figured she was headed home
for the holidays.
And you saw her leave?
Well, no, but luggage was gone.
Room key on the bed,
with a note that said
"Thanks for the stay."
Most folks don't even
leave a note.
Why is this locked?
I don't know.
What's that?
Something Molly would
never leave behind.
suspenseful music
Hey, fuck-o.
Why all this plastic?
You know the concept
of leave no trace?
Well, it's all the more
important here.
A single drop of blood, a single
hair left behind, a print...
anything can lead
to getting caught.
And the Code says,
don't get caught.
That's right.
How many times
have you done this?
-A lot.
-How many?
Go big or go home.
In the hundreds.
Holy shit.
Th-That means
you've saved, like,
thousands of innocent people.
That's right.
You ready?
If there's any moment
where you don't feel up to this
or you feel overwhelmed,
you just head outside.
No shame.
The first time is...
a lot.
Shit!
What the fuck?!
Hey, it's okay.
Shh...
Stop struggling. Shh.
It's the end of the road,
Kurt Caldwell.
Why are you doing this?
Well, look around you, Kurt.
And spare us that old chestnut
about how your father
did this, too.
Okay.
Yeah, you got me.
It's all me.
Every bit of it.
Pretty fucking amazing, huh?
Really?
You-you fucking murdered women.
No! I saved 'em.
They're just runaways.
Do you have any idea
the trauma
that they were gonna
go through?
I do. I saw it.
I saw it firsthand,
what my dad would do to them.
Hey! I told you no dad shit.
I'd pick them up on the road,
and I'd take 'em to my cabin,
and I'd give them a nice room
and a warm meal.
And safety.
But that was never enough
for them.
They always wanted
to go back out there.
And so I preserved them,
kept them safe forever.
Bullshit.
This wasn't
about saving anyone,
this was about power.
You loved the power
you had over them.
It fed the darkness inside you.
You loved
the hunt, the capture.
Their terror feeding you.
You deserve to die.
Oh, wow, Jimbo.
You really get me,
don't you?
So what is this?
You and your son, you're
some kind of vigilante team?
No, don't get me wrong.
I'm kinda jealous.
All the time that
I spent with Harrison.
Kinda made me wish
my son was more like H here.
Yeah, then why'd you try
to kill me?
Oh, shit. He doesn't know.
He doesn't know what
you did to Matt, does he?
Revenge... for your dear old dad
murdering my son.
Eye for an eye.
Son for a son.
Nothing personal, kid.
Matt fit The Code.
Five people died
because of him.
And they didn't
receive justice
because Kurt
covered for him.
Wait. What?
That's your rationale
for killing people?
Some kind of bullshit
justice code?
You know, When Matt was
on my table,
he blamed you for everything.
Just like you blame your dad.
Like father, like son.
You don't have to watch.
No, I'm good.
You okay?
I think so.
If you need to
head up and get some air...
'Cause my work isn't done here.
He has to be disposed of.
I'm ready.
Can you get the garbage bags?
I generally cut them
into nine pieces,
depending on how big they are,
for ease of transport.
eerie synthesizer music
You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Um, I'm gonna go get some air,
like you said.
Hey.
You put these bags
in the back of the RTV?
What happens when people
notice he's missing?
Well, he covered that for us
when he rushed home to escape.
Angela'll look to his place
and see that he ransacked it,
packed his bags, grabbed all
his money from the safe.
You knew he'd run.
Everyone here in Iron Lake
will think he fled.
People run away
from their lives all the time.
No more women kidnapped
and killed.
That's right.
And the Dark Passenger?
Is quiet.
That's how it works.
That's how we keep it
under control.
And the world's
a better place for it.
That's the idea.
Let's go home.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is that smoke?
Harrison.
Oh, my God.
I thought you were dead.
Where were you?
Like I said, I took Harrison
out to see the blood moon.
What the hell happened here?
Well, I was hoping
you could tell us.
It's Kurt's parting shot.
I kept calling you.
Why didn't you answer?
I turned my phone off.
I'm trying to stay present
for Harrison, you know?
What time did you leave?
It was around 10 p.m.
We took the RTV out,
had a great night.
Just lost track of time,
I guess.
They have to stay with us.
What?
It's okay.
We can stay at the inn.
Mom, they can stay
with us, right?
Bet you're starving.
Yep.
-Me, too.
I was thinking eggs and bacon?
Maybe some of those
frozen hash browns?
And a damn fine cup of coffee.
I should probably help
the kids in the kitchen.
Breakfast wizard.
haunting piano music
mysterious music