The Amazing Race
was inspired by two friends
backpacking through Europe,
traveling
from country to country
on a complex network
of rail lines
that extend into more than 40
closely connected nations.
This season will take place here
in the birthplace of democracy
in an awe-inspiring,
one-of-a-kind
European adventure.
We've invited some of Big
Brother'sfavorite contestants
to get out of the house
and compete in the real world
with their favorite
traveling companions.
Big Brother's
strongest competitors...
TUCKER:
I brought my brother.
We're the most
competitive people ever.
KEOGHAN:
...biggest personalities...
ANGELA:
This is my daughter Lexi.
I want to make this
happen. I want to win.
KEOGHAN:
...and celebrated winners...
JAG:
Jas-- he's my brother.
I'm very confident that
we can winThe Amazing Race.
This season is
about to be crazy.
This is my dad Jack.
Let's get another win.
KEOGHAN:
...will battle it out
in Europe's
most iconic locations.
Nothing can prepare them
for anAmazing Race
with more trains...
- It's canceled?
We had a leg up.
Now it looks like
we have a leg down.
...self-driving...
We're driving in circles.
If you just read off these directions,
I could do better driving.
Ugh.
...and racing on foot...
Oh, cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
- Oh, my gosh, be careful.
- Oh, that's okay.
...than ever before.
I guess I never had
to deal with this.
We always had Uber.
KEOGHAN:
They'll face Amazing Race classics...
You didn't just win
one Express Pass.
I have a second one
in my pocket right here.
- Oh!
...spread out
over thousands of miles.
JACK P.:
We are sure not
in New Jersey, man,
I'll tell you that.
Yeah, cow manure!
Ooh.
KEOGHAN:
Relationships will be tested
in ways
they could never imagine...
Are you okay?
Let's not waste time.
Let's just get it done.
Oh, my God.
...and past rivalries reignited.
I played on a season
of Big Brotherwith Izzy.
We have
a complicated relationship.
I can't stand Jas and Jag.
I want to rip their heads off,
I want to yell at them.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
KEOGHAN:
But for those who can
rise above
the fierce competition...
You can do it, sissy.
- Ugh.
- Don't think about it.
- Let's go!
-Good job!
Yeah!
It's gonna be hard.
...they will be rewarded
with a $1 million prize
and be crowned winners
of The Amazing Race.
It all starts right here
in the historic city
of Hoorn in the Netherlands,
where teams are already racing
to their first challenge.
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
All right, here we go!
Right here, right here,
right here, right here,
right here!
Wait, wait, stop,
- stop, stop, stop.
- Let's go, Chels!
- Where are they?
- Go, go, go, go! Go, go, go.
Can you take us to Obtisport?
Yeah?
Great.
Oh, we're the first ones out.
Let's go.
As I'm looking, I'm like,
wait, are...? Is every...?
- Are these...
- All...
- Big Brother?
- Big Brother.
- Yeah.
- I was like, "What's going on?"
There are some people
from my season.
I saw my exes here.
So, I competed
on season 24 of Big Brother
with Taylor.
Taylor and I dated
after the show,
so she is my ex, so...
I guess navigating seeing Taylor
- and Kyland...
- You better, you better be focused.
This race is going to be like
nothing anyone has ever seen.
There's four of us from season
26 of Big Brother,including
Tucker on a separate team
from me.
Tucker is actually my boyfriend.
We met
in theBig Brother house,
and now we are long distance.
I live in L.A.,
he lives in New York.
So we're making it work.
It's on!
This is The Amazing Raceto win.
We have Taylor,
Jag and Chelsea,
who areBig Brother winners.
They're sharp, they're smart.
Everybody is here to win.
Big Brotherall-star season
on The Amazing Race.
A lot of Big Brotherwinners,
too.
I got to learn names, too.
I didn't see half of their
seasons, half of these people.
But it's all good.
It's all good.
Two worlds colliding
right now, right here.
In Deutschland, Amsterdam.
Amsterdam.
- Oh, here's the clue box.
- Oh, right here, right here, right here, right here.
Right there.
Stop, stop, stop. - Stop, stop, stop.
- Got it?
- Let's go. - Excuse me.
Route Info.
KEOGHAN:
Tenpin bowling is popular
with millions of people
around the world.
But here in the Netherlands,
instead of using a bowling ball,
players literally
have their head in the game.
The first team
to get a strike...
will win the Express Pass...
and can skip any task
they don't want to complete
before the end
of the eighth leg.
And the last team
to knock over all the pins
will be burdened with a hazard--
a penalty
they'll have to serve sometime
during this leg of the race.
- Okay. Let's do it.
- All right, let's go.
- All right. Let's go.
- "On a team." Let's go.
- Okay. Great.
- Okay.
"First come, first serve."
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go. Come on.
- Oh! What does it say?
- Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
Take it out. Take it out.
- Ready? Got it all? Thank you.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
I got it.
Mom, was there a clue box
over there?
What's it say?
Go, go, go, come on!
Oh, Tuck, right here.
- Right here, Taylor.
- We got to stay with you.
-Did we miss it?
- What?
JAG:
We noticed that, like,  teams had clues in their hands.
And we didn't see the clue box.
We thought
the clue box was gonna be inside
the building, maybe.
Let's turn back.
We missed a clue out there.
How did we do that?
- We have to go back.
- Okay. We have to go back.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I got this. You walk.
Let's go.
Oh, right there.
Damn.
It's okay. All right.
Okay.
That's not happening again.
- Okay.
- Rip it open.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go, baby.
Whoa.
Aah!
Okay.
Need this Express Pass, baby.
Oh, that's it. Aah.
Now!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
- You got to push me harder.
- I know.
Just make sure you go straight.
- Get me straight.
- Yeah, I got you.
OnBig Brother,
I was strategic,
but I also was very physical.
I just didn't let some
of my teammates know that I was.
So I played
a very, very smart game,
and that's the thing
that got me to the end.
Almost. Almost had it.
WinningBig Brother,
there's gonna be a huge target
on our back,
but I'm here to play,
I'm here win.
We're gonna get this, baby.
- Right here.
- Oh, you found it?
We're not gonna be last
and we're not
- gonna get that hazard.
- Okay.
No!
- Damn it.
-Oh!
That's a good one.
That might be a good one.
No!
Come on. We got to get
out there. We're the last team.
All right, let's go.
Hard, hard. As hard as you can.
Why are you spreading
my butt cheeks?
Come on.
Oh, no!
Go! Got it?
Oh, so close! So close!
- You almost had it.
- I know, right?
- You guys were so close.
- I know!
Let's do it, baby.
Bring it home. Bring it home.
- Oh.
- Missed it.
Good job, guys.
You're killing it. - Ooh.
I was on the same season
as Kyland.
And then,
we actually lived together
for, like, two years after.
It's safe to say we probably
drove each other nuts,
but I feel really good
about my relationship
with Kyland now.
He is like a big brother to me.
I'm gonna smash you, bro.
Yo, get your head in the game.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- It's hard to catch it.
It's hard
to get your foot traction.
I'm a good tracker. Let's go.
-All right, here we go.
- Damn it.
- Oh, well, dang.
- That's okay.
Aah, dang it.
No!
You stay tight and do exactly
what you've been doing, babe.
I got you.
Let's go!
Oh, my God!
And they got it. Damn it!
- Got you, babe.
- Let's take it.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Nice!
- All right, we got the Express Pass.
- Let's go.
- We're kind of shaking with excitement.
"Take your taxi
to Grote Kerk on Kerkplain
in Hoorn and find Phil
on the straat road scene."
- Let's do it, babe.
- Let's go.
This is crazy, bro.
Aw, man. That hurts
watching 'em walk off.
Hop in the taxi.
Hop on your side, babe.
Oh, yeah!
Did they get it?
- Yes. Thank God. Oh, my God.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Yeah, let's go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, please!
Let's go, please.
Yes!
Oh, he got it.
-They got it.
As long
as we don't get the hazard
at that end, I think we're good.
- That's the goal. Yeah.
- We're solid. We're solid.
- We have our Express Pass, baby!
- Express Pass!
- Let's go!
- We got the Express Pass!
Right here. okay.
If we see him, run for it.
- All right, let's go, let's go.
- Let's go, baby.
Yeah, look, look, look.
Right in front of us.
Oh.
Out in front of me here,
- Kat and Alex.
-Oh, my God.
There he is! There's Phil!
- There's Phil!
-Hey!
The party's here!
- Let's go, Phil!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
-All right, go, go.
-
Aw!
Third time is not the charm.
Does anyone have their own lane?
Maybe Jag.
Let's go over there afterwards.
I'm not intimidated by
running this race against Jag.
I wasn't intimidated by him
in theBig Brother house.
I was part of the power
that evicted him unanimously
before a twist saved him,
and then,
he inevitably won.
But no, I'm excited
to race against him.
- I'm excited to beat him.
-Again.
Too much, too much.
Oh, my God!
Aah!
Oh, that's money! That's money!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Come on!
- Yeah!
- Let's go, baby!
It's a little discouraging
seeing more and more teams go.
Yeah!
But it's okay.
Come on!
Go to the left! Move to
the left! Left, left, left! Aah.
What is going on?
-Yeah!
- Oh, my God!
Dang! Dang.
Yay! Ooh.
We'll see Phil.
- I know!
- Finally.
I know.
What a crazy way
to start the race.
What the heck kind of start
was that?
I was like, "Oh, yeah,
we're gonna be in the Pit Stop."
-No.
- "First challenge, now." Whatever you think
- Amazing Racetypically is,
- Buckle up.
buckle up, bitches.
It ain't gonna be that way.
Hey, let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Hey. Oh.
- Aah!
This way. Tuck, Tuck.
Go!
Yeah, let's go!
Run, Steph! Go!
You did it!
Let's go! Let's go!
Aah! Oh.
We have to still finish this.
And last person to do it
gets a hazard. Uh-huh.
Steer it! Steer it, Lexi!
Steer it! Steer it!
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- Oh, we're in trouble.
-Oh, my God.
I can't believe this.
I honestly...
- We got it. We got it.
- I can't believe this.
Damn. Come back, come back,
come back.
Get off of it. Let's go.
You got this!
You got this! You got this!
- Yes! Yes, yes, yes.
- Oh, my God, thank you!
You know, it's okay.
JAS:
Slowly, the teams started just disappearing
until there was literally
three of us left.
And that's when
the pressure was really on,
because we don't want
to get the hazard
- right off the bat.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Nope. Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Yeah!
Oh, my God.
We're gonna
come in dead last, man.
- All right. Okay.
- Thank you.
Yes, baby! Stay straight!
Oh, my God!
That might be a good one.
Bro, we're in trouble here, yo.
We're fighting for last place
right now, bro.
I know, Enzo.
What do you want me to do? - I mean,
this is crazy.
This is crazy.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
- Yes! Let's go!
- They got it, yeah.
That's it.
We got last place. That's it.
- Let's go.
- Aah! Let's go, baby.
Go!
On course!
-Finally!
- Yes.
Let's go! Let's go!
All right, but we don't
have much time to waste.
Come on.
Come on, we don't have much time
to waste. Let's go.
- Yeah, go.
- That's it.
Go, go, go!
Let's go.
Phil!
Yeah!
You guys killed it.
Welcome, everybody,
to the Netherlands.
All right, some of you know
each other because of your time
in the Big Brotherhouse,
some of you don't.
Why don't
you introduce yourselves?
Hi, everyone.
My name is Hannah.
Some of you may know me
as Chaddha.
That's our last name.
This is my
little sister, Simone.
- Hi, everybody.
- Hey.
I'm feeling
incredibly grateful
to share this experience
with my little sister.
Aw, thank you.
Okay, my name's Natalie.
I was on season 18
of Big Brother.
A lot of people think that
we're dating. No, we're not.
This is my blood sister.
We have the same parents.
We came out of the same womb.
Hi. My name is Kat
from Big Brother21.
I'm used to the bitches
conspiring against me.
So this time I brought backup.
This is my boyfriend, Alex.
Hi. I'm Angela Murray,
probably best recognized
for season 26 of Big Brother,
who brought all that mama drama.
I'm here running this race
with my daughter Lexi.
And before you ask, no,
the apple does not
fall far from the tree.
No disrespect, Angela,
but she was
the first
to kind of get a whole
rally of people
against me in the house.
I'm gonna rally
to get Tucker out.
I'm here for you.
And then you try to kick me out.
What did I do to deserve that?
It would be fun to U-Turn her
and her daughter, for sure.
I've dreamt about that
a couple times.
My name is Paige,
and I asked Izzy to marry me
about 48 hours after
she took off the pig costume
and walked out
of the Big Brotherhouse.
That's right.
And we're doing it
for the queers.
We're doing it for the queers! -
My name's Enzo.
I'm here representing
with my best friend,
my little brother Jack.
And it's just, uh,
just an honor.
You know, grateful to be here.
Okay, want to say
congratulations to our team--
Kyland and Taylor--
who won the Express Pass today.
I do need to tell you
that you didn't just win
one Express Pass.
What?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, my God.
I have a second one
in my pocket right here.
And it's up to you
to decide who is going
to get that second Express Pass.
Oh!
Mess. Mess.
- No pressure.
-You want to think very carefully
about this because
this is a chance for you to do
a little strategizing.
Okay, have you made a decision?
Jag and Jas.
Thank you guys.
Thank you... very much.
As much as I wanted
to help out Hannah,
and as much as Taylor wanted
to help out Joseph,
at the end of the day,
we figured
that the relationships
we have with those people
naturally should hopefully
be enough that
they want to work with us,
regardless of us giving them
the Express Pass.
We love you guys,
truly. - Thank you.
- Very hard. Very hard.
- We love you.
KYLAND:
So maybe we could use this Express Pass
to make
a brand-new relationship.
That was hard.
It doesn't hurt
to keep another winner
protected in this game.
KYLAND:
Hopefully, they do well
and can help us out
when we need it.
We'll do anything that we can
to repay you back.
Jack and Enzo,
unfortunately,
you're the last team
to get a strike.
So that means that you will be
penalized with a hazard
sometime
during this leg of the race,
and you're gonna have
to fight really hard
to try to catch up
with the other teams.
- It's a hole but, you know,
- Down but not out.
we got to...
we got to climb out of it.
- That's all.
- Down but not out.
I tell you what.
Should we get this race started?
Your next clue is on the cars
around the corner.
Is everybody ready to race?
The world is waiting for you.
Good luck.
Travel safe.
Go!
You got it, baby!
- Take that one.
- Read it.
Go, go, open it.
Okay.
"Drive yourselves
to Port of Volendam."
"And search along the waterfront
to find your next clue."
Okay. Port of Volendam.
Can we get your help, please?
We're trying
to get to the Port of Volendam.
Here, babe.
Can you put this on your feet? - Yup.
Appreciate you guys, again.
-Good luck.
-Yup.
You, too. See you there, man.
- And we are off.
- We are off.
You're saying
the water should be on our left?
That is what I'm saying. - Are you sure?
I wrote down,
"Stay left along the water."
That's what
you told me to write down.
KYLAND:
I know, but if you're
navigating, we got to...
It's not...
Like, we're-we're...
We got to both look
at the map, you know? Um...
I was on Big Brother23.
And I was on Big Brother24.
- I won the game.
- KYLAND: We met postBig Brother.
When it comes to
our relationship, I feel like
we have
super strong chemistry,
but we have these
communication issues between us
because we both communicate
in such different styles.
TAYLOR:
Like, is this actually going to work or not?
That's why we're here.
Taylor was like,
"I'm gonna give the Express Pass
to the best challenger
in Big Brotherhistory
'cause you need it."
They're the last people
that needed help
- on the race.
- Yeah.
Jag has won
the most competitions
in Big Brotherhistory.
Out of nowhere,
we are now in possession
of an Express Pass,
which is huge for us.
JAG:
We're hoping people don't hold on
to the fact
that I've won before.
But that is something
that we have to think about.
We are the jack-of-all-trades.
I majored in three
different things in college.
- I'm, like, the book-smart nerd.
- He's very smart.
And I'm more
street smart.
We definitely have
what it takes
to win. Yes.
JAG:
This is notBig Brother.
You can't just vote us out.
We hope
to haunt these teams
in their nightmares.
It's right here somewhere. We're
gonna be on the waterfront.
That's a waterfront?
It looks like it to me, buddy.
Good, just park and we'll walk.
All right, we got this.
This looks like a port, dude.
I see some water.
Right here, let's go!
Let's go, baby!
Route Info.
KEOGHAN Per capita,
the Dutch ride their bikes
more than any other country
in the world.
Teams will now ride in tandem
to their next destination.
Except for Jack and Enzo,
who will be faced with a hazard:
having to eat one herring each
before trying to catch up
with the other teams
on this cumbersome clog bike.
Does it have a tandem bicycle?
- Dude.
- Oh, dude's on front!
Are we first, dude?
- We're first place, baby!
- Let's go!
Do you guys know where
the Edam Cheese Market is?
- Oh, I...
- Go straight and then left.
All right, great. Thank you.
Thank God we don't got
to eat that stinky fish.
- Tandem biking.
- Let's go.
"Travel by tandem bike
to Edam Cheese Market
to find your next clue."
Going to the Edam
Cheese Market, baby. - Edam Cheese Market. Mwah.
I was on Big Brotherseason 26.
I was known for going balls to
the wall and calling people out.
Shook the house up.
Chelsie won our season
ofBig Brother,
but this is
a whole different ball game.
You know,
I love and respect her, but, uh,
I think my brother and I
got this in the bag.
Hey, Eric,
I want to make a heart. -
- Hey!
- Hey! - Let's go.
I think we might be in the front,
or at least one of the top
three teams right now because
of the fact that I didn't see
that many cars go this way.
Excuse me.
Is the cheese mart this way?
-Cheese market, Dad!
- Yeah.
Hey, look at these birds!
They look like Netherland ducks.
Cheese market. We're
looking for a cheese market.
Lexi, you cannot wiggle!
- You cannot wiggle, Lexi!
- I'm not...
Stop wiggling!
I don't know where I'm going.
Hopefully, we're not in last.
Hopefully, other teams
are struggling as much as us.
Keep on going.
We got this. We're doing great.
- Okay, where are we going?
- Left on Z Straat.
Okay.
You're pedaling?
Look at you go.
Okay, press
at the same time. Let's go.
There it is. Cheese market.
Look
for the Edam Cheese Market.
Navigating kicked our butts.
Where can we possibly go?
We need to park.
But, like, where do I go?
Volendam is right here.
See the one road...
Bro, what the...
Look, Enzo.
That sign says
Hotel Volendam in there.
So now, that's Hotel...
Well, do we risk it
and keep driving that way?
I-I don't think we're going
to a waterfront anymore, man.
I feel like there... I feel like
there could be a hundred ports.
I feel like
everything could be a port.
What even is a port? Like...
My God.
How can a human being
even do this ...?
I mean, we can just park here
- for now and see what we see.
- Yup.
Do you see anything on that side?
Um, no.
I'm curious when we're gonna see what our hazard is.
When are we gonna find that out?
One thing at a time, my guy.
We got to get here first.
That's the cheese mart!
Let's go! - Oh, this looks right, baby.
- Hey!
- Come on!
Yeah!
Route Info.
KEOGHAN:
Edam cheese is instantly
recognizable here
in the Netherlands
because of its shape
and yellow wax coating.
Teams need
to pick up 30 bowls of them
from the vendors on these boats,
then, tossing them
two at a time,
carefully stack them
on these traditional carriers
and deliver them
to the big cheese
who's gonna be waiting
for them in a nearby market.
And once they've made their
delivery, they'll get a clue.
"Choose any available cheese
carrier." All right, cool.
Okay, while we read it,
let's go change.
We had to deliver cheese
the traditional Dutch way.
So we had to dress up
in these Dutch cheese men
outfits.
- We were... we were cheesing.
-
How do we do this?
- Oh!
- Like, this?
- Okay. Yeah? - Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's start walking. - Okay.
- To the cheese! Let's go!
- To the cheese!
Yeah!
Okay, you can pick up the pace.
Let's go!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Onward!
- Let's go!
Oh, it's down there. Let's go!
Right here. Right here.
Place it right here.
- Next one.
- Yeah.
Wait. Don't we have
to get cheese or what?
Yeah,
from the guys on the boats.
They're gonna throw us
two at a time.
We got to match
that stack over there.
-Oh, man.
-Oh, God. - TUCKER: Cheese!
Okay, that's what it's supposed to look like.
Pyramid. Got it.
Yeah!
Okay.
Jaga, how many total do we need?
Four, three, two, one.
Just start stacking 'em.
JAG:
We had to just make this cheese look
exactly like the example.
So we just counted,
you know, the rows.
- It's a pyramid. A base of a...
- A layer of fours,
- threes, twos, and then ones.
- Yes.
- Oh!
- Ah. Yeah!
We're catching cheese!
JAS:
And so, all I did is, the flattest end that it had,
I just put on the ground,
I packed it tight.
Ah!
Nothing too major.
- Good. Good work.
- One, two, three, four.
No, no. Look, look, look.
We got to make sure
those are flat. - I know.
Go grab more. I got this.
The more that's piled up,
the more the weight's gonna
be on the bottom,
and they're not gonna shift.
You need a sturdy base.
- You only need those two more.
- Yeah.
Uh, you might be good.
That's done.
- Do it quicker.
- And then just one.
Let's make sure.
- Yeah, it is. It is.
- Yup, we're good.
All right, you take the front?
They're very waxy and rolly,
so they do not want to stay put.
- Just keep grabbing more, dude.
- Yeah, this is tough, dude.
I'm telling you,
that's gonna help.
Nice and slow, nice and slow.
- Up. One, two, three, up.
-One, two, three.
- We got to go.
-Oh, heavy. Slow.
There you go. Okay.
- Don't let it sway.
- Yes.
Once the weight's on, dude, I'm telling you.
Well, I know, but we have
to wedge 'em in there first. We
have to get, like, a solid base.
We can't just
keep stacking 'em. - They're already gone.
I'm watching, I'm watching,
-Okay.
- uh, which one's moving.
It's only the top one.
It's pretty sturdy.
- Put them in the wedge.
- Yeah.
They're just gonna
keep rolling that way.
These are round, waxy,
slippery balls.
Cheese!
Go for it.
Go for it right there. Drop.
So...
- Yeah!
- Yeah! Let's go!
All right, let's go.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you!
All right,
there's our clue box!
"Stack and deliver cheese
the Dutch way
to receive your next clue."
Route Info.
KEOGHAN:
Teams will ride their bicycles
back to the Port of Volendam,
then drive themselves
to Van der Wilt Gerbera's
in the town of Mijdrecht
to find their next clue.
- Okay, let's just...
- Perfect, bro. -
- Yeah, let's go!
-Outfits! Let's go!
Let's make some cheese,
or do something
with some cheese.
Who do you want to pick?
- It doesn't matter.
- Let's go with these guys.
Let's go
with this guy right here.
- Red, yeah!
- Okay.
- Stand up.
- Yeah, ready?
Yup.
All right, just...
It went. It went. Stop. Stop.
- Damn, dude.
- It's all right, dude.
TUCKER:
It was just tough 'cause some of the...
It was, like, almost
a perfect sphere, but, like,
some of them had a little more
flatter side on 'em,
but other ones
weren't as flat, so,
it was getting, like, annoying.
Just got to keep going.
Another team's coming in.
Now where are we going?
Oh, there it is.
- Set it down?
-Dude.
- Down, Chelsie.
-This is ridiculous.
I got it.
Okay!
I like that, man.
Like, we have to be in the right
- damn spot.
- Yeah.
Just keep... going.
JACK P.:
Let's go, Enzo. Let's go.
We got to start running, man.
-That's our hazard.
-Oh.
We got to do this
before anything.
Oh, man, I think
we are the last team, man.
Let's see what this is.
"Eat a herring,
then ride off on your clog bike
to Edam Cheese Market
to find your next clue."
- What is that?
- Oh, my God.
Eat one herring?
ENZO:
Because we came in last at the bowling challenge,
we had to do
this hazard penalty.
It was, uh,
not our finest moment.
You're gonna eat it like this.
-Like that?
- Yes.
How you gonna eat this thing?
This thing's slippery as hell.
I don't have to worry
about the pickles, right?
No, just grab it like this,
by the tail,
and then you got to eat it.
That's it.
We're gonna throw up,
that's all.
Oh, my God.
All the way up to the tail?
I think you're pretty good.
It's a little slimy, right?
It's, like, a little slimy,
- a little soft, a little warm.
- Yeah. Ew. Yeah.
I was like, "Ah, I don't
know." You know what I mean?
And we got to do the bicycle thing.
Every time
I've done Big Brother,
I've made it to a finals,
but I've never won, you know?
So, now to go onThe
Amazing Race with my brother,
this is it. Like, this is
definitely my redemption time.
I got to take this one down.
Enzo, you got...
yeah, you got to hold on to it.
Yeah, you're heavy, bro.
I'm not liking me being
in this seat right here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
All right.
We're gonna crash 17 times.
The hazard, the hazard.
Oh, watch out. Be careful
over there, all right?
- We got to...
- I'm riding the brake. I'm not even pedaling.
I'm going crazy right now.
- All right.
- Let's keep going.
Could it be on that dock?
Could it be right here?
Could that duck be it?
This is adorable, where we're at.
- Bump right here.
- Ooh, thank you.
I can't believe
we're riding a tandem bike. - This is crazy.
We're doing a good job.
Look, look,
there's another team.
Doing good.
We have won as many Tour de Frances as Lance Armstrong.
Biking in the Netherlands.
We're biking
in the Netherlands. Holla.
You pedaling back there?
Come on, girls!
- Aah!
- Aah, that's it! Aah.
- Let's go.
- Lexi!
Angela, are you okay?
You might be better at driving
a car, but you're not better
at driving a freaking bike!
This isn't your typical
mother and daughter
relationship.
We're more of a friendship,
I would say.
ANGELA:
But I'll always be mommy, number one.
Lookit, she's my youngest,
and I worry about her.
Like, I can't go to sleep till
I know she's in her apartment.
LEXI:
She has an AirTag in my car. What else?
Oh, I follow you
on your phone, too, because
- I need to know where she is.
- She will follow me on my phone.
She... I wouldn't be surprised
if she flew to Vegas
to see where I was.
I've contemplated that,
I'm not gonna lie.
You about killed your mother. - LEXI: I'm so sorry.
Okay, let's ask for directions.
We got some cushion.
I'm looking, not seeing.
Could we use your phone
to navigate
to Van der Wilt Gerbera's?
We're in a race.
Look, we can keep our eyes open.
It's down there.
- It's down there.
- It's down there. - MEGAN: Thank you!
- Thank you! Thank you!
-And you got to bike
a while.
Like, it's deep. It's deep.
-So...
- Oh, waterfront.
- Right down here?
-Okay, well.
Okay.
Wait. They just walked right by it.
- Matt!
-Hey!
- Yeah!
- Turn here! Right here, right there!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
-Okay.
- We found it!
Thank you.
It only helps us to help them.
We're ahead, so...
Keep on your right.
Like, follow this path.
You'll see, like,
signs for Edam.
Oh, this is a fun activity
for us. - Yeah.
At least we can
kind of just enjoy this.
Yeah.
Instead of trying to figure out where we're going.
Actually, we are doing that,
as well. - Yeah.
We are officially the Turners.
We got married back
in October, 2023,
and everything is... Oh, 23?
24? Wait, wait, wait.
We need
to get our memory better. - Oh, my God. Hold on.
We're having fun. It's a honeymoon.
- Yeah, you're right.
- It's okay.
Off into the sunset we go.
Two more. There we go.
Line 'em up like this.
- Hold on.
-'Cause when you carry it,
it's gonna be off-balance.
We have to be very gentle,
okay, Dad?
There you go. A little bit
that way. You're good.
Okay.
Just keep going straight here.
- Damn it.
- There. Whoa.
All right, there we go.
Oh, these look pretty sturdy
right now.
- Oh, shoot.
- All right.
- Which way? Same way?
To the left.
Good. Good.
Delivering cheese,
the Dutch way.
Here, here, here.
This has got to be it.
I'm smelling cheese!
That's a sign we're close.
All righty.
Ready? Nice and slow.
One, two, three.
Izzy, right here. We found it.
-We did it!
- Okay.
Okay, get the clue.
How do they look?
It's okay?
- Let's go!
- Ah, let's go! Thank you, sir.
We get to dress in a costume!
"Back to the Port..."
- Good job, guys. Good job.
- "of Volendam."
Then drive ourselves somewhere.
All right, let's go.
- Dad, Dad, Dad, look.
- Oh, shoot.
Route Info.
"Stack and deliver cheese..."
"...the Dutch way
to receive your next clue."
- Okay, let's go.
- Okay, lower. Good.
All right, Judge.
- Yeah!
- Yeah! Let's go!
JAG:
"Drive yourselves to Van der Wilt
Gerbera's."
We're in the right area.
Oh, I see it.
I see it. I see it. - Through this line four...
Clue box, clue box, clue box.
All right.
- Roadblock!
- Roadblock. Okay.
"Who's feeling fresh
as a daisy?"
The Netherlands
is often referred to
as the flower capital
of the world.
The flower power here
is so strong,
it's this country's
number one export
and a major draw for tourists.
This enormous greenhouse,
about the size
of six football fields,
houses 42 varieties of flowers.
This Roadblock requires teams
to find and pick
nine of them...
...paying careful attention
to the color and pedals.
Once they've arranged them
in a display box just like this,
the bloom boss
will hand them a clue.
- I think you do it.
- You think I should do it? We got...
- We have a lead.
- Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
- Oh, baby.
- Oh, my God.
- All right, let's do it.
- All right, let's go.
- How's it going?
- Welcome.
Oh, I love... I love the jacket.
That looks great.
-This is the card.
- Okay, this is what it looks like.
Maroon,
black in the middle.
I had to look
at an example of flowers...
Yellow-black, pink-yellow.
- Everything in the mind?
- Yes.
...and then run
into the greenhouse
and find those exact matches.
This is beautiful!
What?!
This is crazy.
There are so many red ones.
There are so many
different pink ones.
This one looks like this was it.
This is... correct.
Pink-yellow. I do need
pink-yellow,
but I'm gonna make sure
this is the correct pink-yellow.
It's getting hot in here.
I might have
to shed some layers.
We just park it
back here, right? - Yeah.
We made it.
We are ready to go.
-Whoa.
-Oh, wow, they're fast.
Me and my dreams
just standing up and going.
Literally the hardest day
of my life.
Yo, we're on an adventure.
We don't know where we're going.
We don't know where--
Edam.
Adam and Eve.
I don't know
what's going on, my man.
SIMONE:
"Stack and deliver cheese
the Dutch way..."
"...to receive your next clue."
- I'm breaking, I'm breaking.
- Aah! - Oh, my goodness!
- Yes! Yes!
- It does exist! - Right, right!
- Let's go. Good job.
- All right. Thank you.
- Do you have the clue?
- Yeah.
Okay, we got to put on clothes.
We're in need of help. We're a little lost.
We're trying
to find Edam Cheese Market.
The Edam Cheese Market.
- Edam?
- Cheese. - Edam Cheese Market.
- Across the bridge.
-Yeah... - Let's go. Let's go.
- We're good. We're good.
- Hi, guys.
Hey, guys. Good luck.
- Right?
- Sorry. So we're going...
Let's go.
-Good job, good job.
- It's very heavy.
Taylor,
are you walking? - Y'all are fine.
Nice.
- It's very good.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Ready? Get on.
- Come on.
- Ugh. Please, please, please.
- Yeah!
- Thank you. Thank you so much!
- Oh!
Oh, hey, we got to hurry.
-So we're down in here.
- Yeah. Yes.
Let's see what this is about.
What else do we have to lose, bro?
Yeah, whatever.
Come on, man, you know.
Yeah, we're in people's backyards,
- people's basements.
- Yeah.
I'm telling you, this is bad.
- Yeah, this is bad.
- Yeah, worst... worst team ever
on The Amazing Race.
If you think
you have what it takes
to win The Amazing Race,
then go to cbs.com/casting
and apply now.
The world is waiting for you.
I'm so sorry. We're in a race,
and we're lost right now.
We're trying
to find Edam Cheese Market.
- Edam Cheese Market?
- Yeah.
- Cheese market. Yeah. All the way straight out.
We're gonna pass the cheese
factory and keep going that way?
Yeah, yeah.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Keep going.
- Bro, I'm telling you.
- Thank you.
- All right, you ready?
- Bro, this is insane, bro.
Let's go.
Insane, bro.
Go ahead. We're gonna
make a left over here.
That looks like a clue box
to me, dude.
- Roadblock.
- Roadblock, baby.
I'm feeling pretty fresh.
What do you think?
Yeah, you think
you can do it with... - Yeah.
- Oh, yeah. Yo.
- How we doing? How we doing?
- You look like the flower boss.
- Welcome, welcome.
Great to meet you.
Dude, this is hard as ...
Yellow, green in the middle.
Oh, baby.
- Right? Right?
- Oh, man, dude.
Yo, do you have any already
that you can point me to?
I have some. Um...
Can you show me
where you got those?
Yes. I believe, one...
And then...
And then we can work
on the next ones together.
Yeah, I think one
of these is one of them.
You want me
to grab the pink ones for you
- and just run down there?
- Yeah.
JAS:
I essentially gave him
the answers, and then I made
him do the running 'cause
I was exhausted at that point.
Let's go, Eric.
Ooh.
I think that's good.
It's good.
It's so far.
Just got to keep pedaling.
It doesn't help
that I have the calf muscles
of Woody from Toy Story.
I don't see teams, bro.
It's all over - They go to...
- for us, bro.
- This is crazy.
We look like idiots, bro.
I mean, just come on.
We're looking stupid here.
Okay, communicate. Please.
Okay, you lead,
and I will follow, right?
You tell me where to go.
It looks like most of the teams
are here with us.
One, two, three,
four other teams.
- Yeah. Steph.
- Aw.
Ooh! Oh.
Right in the knockers.
Push this back
a little bit more.
This row needs to get stable
first before we add more.
Oh.
Okay, I see what you're saying.
- This is the last of the cheese.
-Oh, okay.
- Thank you for doing that.
- Of course.
Okay.
Yeah, and then
put one right here.
- Okay.
- Good job.
People ask
how long we've been together,
and it's kind
of a loaded question.
We've known each other
since 2017.
I'm a full-time influencer.
He reached out to me
and a couple
of my friends
to do a photo shoot.
The photos were beautiful,
by the way.
- The photos were amazing.
- Yeah.
We hated each other
at first. I...
ALEX:
She was really mean.
- I was so mean to him.
- Yeah.
A couple years later,
I texted him, and I was like,
"Hey, I'm so sorry
for how I acted."
From there, it kind of stemmed
into a friendship.
From there, it stemmed
into we started
working together full-time.
- Um, now we're dating.
- We're dating.
- And... Yeah.
- Now we're here.
- Here you go.
- And then that's it.
- That's it.
- All right.
Start in a lunge, Simone, and then come up.
-Okay. Are we up?
- Yeah, we're...
Oh, okay, be careful...
Oh, my gosh!
- Did it fall?
- Wait. This ripped.
-Slowly.
-Okay, wait.
-All right, we good?
- Oh, my gosh.
-Walk so slowly.
-Yeah.
I don't feel good
about the strength of this,
but let's see it.
Left, right,
left, right, left.
-My hat! My hat! My hat!
- Right.
Can you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Stand, stand, stand.
- They're walking really fast.
- Okay.
We're not that fast.
- Watch your hat.
- As we slowly pass.
- Hey, watch your hat.
- Hold your hat, yup.
Do you want to be back here
so you can watch it, or no?
I'm following your lead.
- No, you're killing it, babe.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Yeah! - Yes!
I was about to say, yeah!
- Oh, my God!
- Thank you.
You have made a fantastic stack.
- Yay!
Thank you.
- Okay, that's awesome.
- Yes! - Yeah!
- Oh, my God. Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you so much, sir.
Maybe it's it right out there.
The ma... Oh, did I
drop the map? Pull it back.
I dropped the map.
What a mess.
Okay, we're moving.
Slow and steady.
Slow and steady. - Okay.
I'm feeling good.
I'm feeling really good.
Steph, we have to hurry up.
This can't be happening
right now.
Hey, I think we can afford
to go a little faster. - Okay.
-Careful. Wobbly.
- This is really pushing me.
I know. This is really heavy.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Hey, okay, we need patience.
Growing up, my mom was trying
to just get stability
as a single-parent household.
And we really had
to rely on each other more
than a lot of siblings do.
So we kind of had this,
like, parent relationship
where we kind of
boss each other around.
But it got to the point
where we both needed
to grow individually
to come back together
and have that respect
for each other.
So, that is what I'm hoping
we get out ofThe Amazing Race
is a friendship.
- We need to re-strategize.
- Whatever.
- Yay!
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you!
Okay.
- Yeah!
-Thank you!
We're good.
It's adding pressure.
All right, nice and slow, okay?
Okay. We got it.
-Hey, hey, there we go.
- Park, park, park.
Okay, somebody just got here.
"Stack and deliver cheese
the Dutch way
to receive your next clue."
Look, Steph, be careful.
It's going up the hill.
Okay. We're okay, Nat.
We're at an angle, Steph.
- Steph. Steph.
- Relax!
Yeah, I'm carrying all the weight.
- So we're in this, baby.
- Let's go.
Wonderful stack, so it is okay.
- Yes!
- Thank you.
-Thank you.
- Oh, my God.
You guys just came back from the Edam Cheese Market?
- Yeah.
-They just came back from there.
Enzo, let's go, man.
Can we just get our head
in the game?
Man, this is a beautiful...
- It is beautiful.
- ...beautiful little town.
Oh, my gosh, wait, I still have my thing on.
- The what?
- My bandana.
I still have this bandana on.
I just know
that if we don't return this,
I didn't know what was going
to be the penalty,
but I knew
that something was coming.
We have to figure this out.
- Let me see.
- Here.
"Leave your wardrobe..."
Well, I know. I'm sorry.
But... all we can do
is drive back. - Yeah.
But we got to figure out
how to get there.
On our way
to the Van der whatever.
- All right, come on.
- Oh, man.
-Here we go.
-Oh, my God.
- Here we go.
- Is this really cheese?
- Is it?
- I don't know.
This looks good.
Yeah, let's go.
- You got it.
- It's like the world's
- hardest squat.
- Now, nice and easy.
Nice and easy. Now let's go.
-Oh, yeah.
- Let's go, cheese.
We're gonna find it, okay?
- Come on, babe.
- I know.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- I-I know, but
- I need... I need a second.
- I know.
- I'm just really frustrated.
- I know. Babe, it's...
Any-Anybody can make
that mistake.
Babe, we'll figure it out,
I promise.
Oh, my God, I'm such an idiot.
Babe, you're not.
Everyone could
have made that mistake.
I could have made-- anyone
could have made that mistake.
I think we're good.
I think we can drive back here,
drop that off,
and then go to the van.
Perfect. Right here.
You can jump out whenever.
We did it.
I need to figure out a better
way to organize these things.
This is like an extreme sport.
- You're good.
- I feel like I'm gonna have a baby.
Yes, this stack is okay.
- Thank you. Yes.
- Thank you.
- Here... I want to give you...
All right, check.
- Not good.
- No?
- Okay.
JAS:
The pink row is incorrect.
- Thank you.
- I know the mistake already.
- This one?
- Yes.
- They're working together.
-Yeah.
This is it for sure, dude.
Let's do this.
-Is this it?
- Yeah, right here, right here.
-Oh, my God.
- Get the clue, get the clue.
Right here. Park right here,
right here, right here.
Bro, get out, yo.
Come on, let's go.
I've been driving you
the whole time. Let's go.
- Bro.
- Come on, Enzo.
Let's go.
Roadblock.
- Maybe I do it.
- Feels up your alley.
Okay, I'm gonna do it.
Anything sort of artistic
or, like, creative--
that's what
I'm going to take on.
Check.
Come on. Come on!
- It's good.
- Yeah. Let's go! - Let's go!
Yeah, let's go!
See y'all soon. Whoo!
- It's good.
- Baby, let's go!
- Congratulations.
- Let's go! Let's go!
-Appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
- Whoo! Route Info.
- Route Info.
"Race to your very first
Pit Stop."
KEOGHAN:
Art enthusiasts
here in the Netherlands say that
it ain't much unless it's Dutch.
And coincidentally,
two of the world's most popular
museums are right here
in Amsterdam at Museum Square--
the Van Gogh
and the Rijksmuseum.
This is where teams will find
their first Pit Stop
on their European adventure.
The last team to check in here
will be eliminated.
You know where the taxi is.
Let's go.
"The last team to check in
will be eliminated."
We got to go to a taxi.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Woo-hoo-hoo! Let's go, baby.
Museumplein, Amsterdam.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
We are racing for first place right now.
Oh, wow.
This is amazing. Oh, my God.
This is, like,
overstimulation overload.
Oh, my God, the subtle
differences. This is legit.
JACK P.:
All right, then, that should be good.
- Okay.
- So now we got to take this back over there.
- This is gonna be hard, bro.
- Just do what we got to do.
Come on.
Easy. Easy.
My back is killing me.
This is it. I think I'm done.
I hate running.
Shall I check you?
- It's not good.
- It's not good. Okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, wow. Okay, okay, okay.
- Not good.
Okay, what's the deal?
What am I not seeing?
You got time.
-Almost there.
-All right, come on, bro.
Okay. Now, I have seen enough.
I think it's also...
- Thank you. My God. Thank you.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
We are going to the Van der Wilt Gerbera's.
Mijdrecht is the town
we are going to park at.
I've never navigated without an iPhone in my life.
"Who's feeling fresh
as a daisy?"
You are!
- I'm a florist.
- She's doing it.
Obviously, you're doing this.
I was hyped.
- Hi.
I'm a florist in L.A.,
so this is very exciting. -
This is her jam!
Walk in the door.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Aah!
Is this not the same flower?
Oh, I guess
it is super pink in the middle.
Let's check the other pink ones.
Let's see.
Oh, my gosh.
It's so warm in here.
This is insane.
It's got a larger green center.
I'm going with this.
This is a very large greenhouse.
They all look...
kind of looks the same, yeah?
That's what I'm saying.
I was really thankful
when Kristine showed up,
who's a florist.
Yeah.
Feeling like
if it's mutually beneficial,
we're happily gonna work
with a team.
Oh. Where's the sun going?
We can't see!
-Oh, no!
- Do they need to turn the lights on?
Oh, my God, it's dark in here!
- Oh, my God, no!
-What happened?
Oh, my God,
is the lighting timed? - Oh, my God.
It's dark as hell!
Is that just a cloud?
Oh, my God, it's pitch black!
I can't see!
I can't see anything!
Maybe the lighting is timed.
The shades go up.
- So it's dark in there.
- Oh.
And it has probably something
to do with, like,
the growing patterns
or what kind of sunlight
they need to grow.
- Headlamp.
-I need a headlamp.
- Get in that clue box. Come on.
- Ah. Oh, my God.
There's a lot in there.
Can you do it?
Attention to detail?
Yeah.
- What's up, ladies?
- Oh, hi. Yes! Yes!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
God! Okay, okay.
All right,
let's start with reds.
I feel bad
picking these flowers.
"Who's feeling fresh
as a daisy?"
- Uh, you.
- Me.
- You want to do it or me?
- I'll do it.
You can do it.
Oh, my God.
You have to be kidding me.
- Izzy!
- What up, baby?
- Hey!
- Hi.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, it is warm.
Oh, golly.
Here we go.
Oh, wow.
- It's good.
- Yes, let's go.
- Yeah.
- Let's go. - Wow.
- Thank you so much, boss.
- Yeah.
That's my girl.
So we're going to Van der Wilt Gerbera's.
Is it that way?
Is it this way?
It's hard
when there's no street signs.
Let me drive, Alex.
I think I got this.
Oh, there's a car behind us.
Oh, it's them.
These guys are literally
right ahead of us right now.
We did our best,
we made it here.
If they beat us in a footrace,
they beat us. That's okay.
Let's get it, dude.
- Let's get it, dude.
- May the best team win.
This is the Museum Square. - Perfect, thank you.
All right, come on, Jaga.
Whoo!
Right there,
right there, right there.
- Where?
- Right there.
- Yeah!
- Oh. - TUCKER: Ooh.
You guys are fast!
- Ooh.
- All right.
- Beautiful.
- Let's go!
He's not on the mat, Jag.
- Let's go.
- Good job, boys. Good job.
Welcome to Amsterdam
in the Netherlands.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you. - Thank you.
You guys raced through
this course. You are teams
number one and two.
Jas and Jag,
you have won $2,500 each.
- Let's go!
- Run it up. Let's go.
JAS:
First place?
We were telling ourselves,
like, that would be insane
with the start that we had.
You know,
the Turbanators ended up
first place today. - Oh, yeah.
- Let's go.
- Turbanators are up big-time.
Parking, parking.
Okay, go.
Roadblock.
- I'll do it.
- Okay. - HANNAH: You want to do it?
Yeah, I did that
for sorority stuff. - Okay, let's do it.
- Can I check?
- Yes, please. Yes, please.
You're doing great, Pulan!
- Um...
-Yeah.
Thank you so much!
-Perfect.
- Thank you!
That's a no.
Yes.
Yes! I'm feeling confident.
- They're not for you!
- Ah!
Not after that Express Pass nonsense!
Oh, shut up.
Holy ...,
there's a lot of people here.
-Okay. Okay.
- Go for it, rip it.
- Can you do it?
- Yeah, I'll do it.
I feel like
you're more levelheaded
- right now than I am.
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
It's really hot and humid.
Oh, this is so pretty.
This is such a fun Roadblock.
This is hell.
Yeah, you made it.
Get those feet on the mat.
- Ah!
- Clock stops right there.
- You are team number three.
- Let's go! -
Listen, we'll take it.
We'll take
what we can get, Phil.
To go from 12th
to third feels pretty good.
Oh, my God, it feels amazing.
- We got to put out its...
- We're going downhill.
- You're going downhill.
- Yo, you...
We're going downhill,
and I'm gonna crash on purpose.
I don't know what it was.
- A banana bowl bike?
- I don't know what it was,
- and I didn't pay attention.
- Pac-Man. I don't know what it was.
Get out, bro.
But it was just the distance
of going to the cheese market
and then back.
It just killed us in time.
But when you're in this
competition, it's just,
"What do we got to do?
What do we got to do?
What do we got to do
to try to catch up?"
Next step, let's go.
Hello. We're looking for this place here.
That's the roundabout,
so we go that way?
- All right.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Honestly, though,
these were the best directions
- I've gotten today.
- I just feel like
I'm fighting a losing battle,
so it's really frustrating.
No, we're winning.
We're not winning,
unfortunately.
Right there, right there, right there.
Living in hell right now.
All right, dude.
- This is...
- Oh, I never thought I would see the day.
"Who's feeling fresh
as a daisy?"
- I guess, uh...
- You.
It is humid in here.
You're exhausted.
I was going
to collect a lot of stuff
and then try
to arrange it there.
I think it's this one.
We're going to give it a shot.
- Which is the one that we need?
- This one.
- Right, you think?
- Yep.
Behind the bins to the right.
I owe you, Chelsie.
Check.
Yes!
I'm so proud of you, tata!
- Let's go!
- Ah.
- Let's go, baby!
- Yes!
Thank you!
Let's go.
Aren't you glad to see us?
Oh, my God, yes.
- Team number four.
- Yeah!
We're going to find our next clue, which is probably
a Roadblock.
If we are going to a Roadblock,
I'm hoping to see a team,
at least one team there.
That gives us some energy,
some life.
Let's see what happens, bro.
-This is Gerbera.
- Hey, we got to hurry.
"Who's feeling fresh
as a daisy?" - Me.
Ugh.
These orange ones
are killing me for some reason.
I'll find this orange somewhere,
somehow.
-Can I get a check?
- Get a check?
Yes. My flower boss.
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
I'm back
with different orange flowers
this time.
Thank you so much! Thank you.
- Yay!
- Oh, my gosh.
Can I have a check, please?
Okay.
- Congratulations.
- Yes!
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
- Good job. Let's go.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Okay, let's go, let's go.
It's going to get harder
when it's darker.
Mm-hmm, definitely.
Oh, that sunset is brutal.
It's getting harder to find...
see the colors.
Dad, up here!
Natalie and Stephanie,
you are team number five.
- Congratulations.
- Yeah!
Jack and Chelsie
are here. - Oh.
- Dad, let's go.
-Let's go!
Jack and Chelsie, guys.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I am pleased to tell you,
Jack and Chelsie,
that you're team number...
- six.
- Six. Yeah! - Yeah!
Good job, guys.
It's just getting harder and harder to see
the colors,
which is really discouraging.
Yellow.
Where do I even go?
I think it's these.
But they look identical!
Is that not
the same exact flower?
Like, I d... I'm so confused.
Check.
Now we see.
Oh!
I got to tell you,
I'm ready to cry.
What is this?
Van der Wilt "Gerber"?
- Here it is.
Guys, you got it.
They just got their clue.
Angela and her daughter.
One clue left.
- I'm exhausted, yo.
- So you want me to do it? I'll do it.
I'll do it. We lose,
I-I... it's my fault.
Don't worry, I'll do it.
Oh, wait a minute,
other people are... - Hey, guys.
- They're all here, right?
- Way to get here.
Yeah.
Sorry. It's not good.
- You're killing me.
-It's okay.
You got this, babe.
- You got it.
- I don't even know what's happening.
I know. It's okay. You got it.
One step at a time.
At a certain point, I didn't
even know what I was changing.
It was, like,
I looked at both sides.
I was like,
"Everything looks right to me."
That was the hardest thing
I've ever done.
Yeah, it's in here.
I am behind,
but there's a fighting chance.
- And we'll go from there.
-Jack just showed up.
This sucks.
It's still not ri...
I think I can't tell.
It's not good.
Sorry.
I'm just... I'm gonna
be here doing this all night
'cause I don't know what it is.
I literally don't know
which one it is.
I'm gonna be here doing this
all night
'cause I don't know what it is.
I literally don't know
which one it is.
You got this.
You can figure this out.
Kat started crying 'cause
she was just so frustrated.
So I was like, "Bro, this is
the perfect opportunity to just
get this done
and get out of here.
- I can't find that one.
-You got it, baby.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
Giovanni and Enzo, let's go.
How about seven?
No way!
You are officially
team number nine.
Oh!
You are team number ten.
Ah!
KAT:
I'm not even trying to be that hard on myself.
I just do not want
to be the first one out.
Maybe I've stumbled
across something.
Think it's this.
Just gonna keep fighting.
I think I'm not gonna stop, bro.
I got to check.
- Oh.
- Let's do this.
- Am I hired?
- Honey, don't cry, huh?
- Thank you.
- Don't cry.
I'm about to lose my mind.
At that point,
it is literally a race
for our lives in this game.
It's a needle in a haystack
in this thing, man.
Oh, did I find you?
Maybe I just found you.
Seems like
I got the correct flowers.
We're in this race, yo.
Now...
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Holy... crap.
"The last team to check in
will be eliminated."
All right, we're on the race.
Aw, thank you so much. Oh, yeah.
Thank you. Yeah.
- Let's go, man. See, yo.
- That's all right.
Oh.
- Phil, it's been a day.
- Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Kat and Alex,
- tough day.
- Yeah. - Very tough.
Well, I'm pleased to tell you
you're team number 11.
- Oh, my gosh.
This day has been
the hardest day of my life,
ten times over.
My favorite part of the day is when
we showed up at the end,
there were still two teams.
Like, it's like they saw
a ghost. It's like, "Wait.
I thought these guys died
a long time ago."
Seeing Phil
is gonna be so nice. - Yeah, it's gonna be...
I don't even know
if he will be there.
Like, genuinely,
what if he went to bed?
Just, you know, I mean, just, we
don't know. We just never knew.
Thank you. So it says "Museumplein."
- All right, yo.
- Let's go, bro. We got a mat.
Ah. All right. Ah.
Overall, it was one
of the hardest days of our life,
but I can't believe
we actually finished
- the leg.
- Break it to me. Are we in last?
Well, in this moment, you need
to know that if you want to,
you will be racing in the
next leg of this Amazing Race.
Let's go. Oh.
Team number 12.
There is one more team
behind you.
You know who it is.
-Yes.
- Yes. They had...
they had the hurdle
they had to get over
halfway through the day.
If it wasn't for that,
- I think we would've been toast.
- I think we would've been gone.
- Yeah.
- There was definitely a savior that...
God's watching out for us,
that's for sure. - Yeah.
-Let's go, bro.
-Come on.
Here we go.
- Here you are, guys.
- We made it.
Unfortunately, Jack and Enzo,
you are the last team
- to arrive here tonight.
- Yeah.
And I am sorry to tell you
that you have been eliminated
from this race.
I'm super proud
of just so many things I've done
in this country that I would
have been terrified to do.
And I wasn't scared at all.
I was just, "Let's go,
let's go, let's go." - We had a good time.
"We got to do this, we got
to do that," you know? So...
We had a good time.
Horrible leg,
but we ended strong.
That's it. It is what it is.
The dynamic
ofThe Amazing Race,
and you're in an element
you have no idea about.
Like, you're...
I'm in a whole other country
I've never been in before.
So you can't come in last,
you've got to make sure
you figure things out,
or else you're gone.
- You had fun? Yeah, that's it.
- Yeah, I had fun.
We didn't even learn
any Dutch though, right?
We didn't even learn,
like, a word, nothing.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Next time
onThe Amazing Race...
Matt's pushed to the limit.
The second I move,
I start shaking.
I can't. This is so scary.
KEOGHAN:
And a train disruption puts teams in jeopardy.
- What?
- It's canceled? It's canceled?
We had a leg up. Now it looks
like we have a leg down.