Previously
onThe Amazing Race...
13 former
Big Brother contestants,
paired with their favorite
traveling companions,
began racing in the Netherlands.
Two worlds colliding right now
in Amsterdam.
Dating couple Kyland and Taylor
won a game-changing
Express Pass...
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
...and strategically handed
a second Express Pass
to another
formerBig Brother winner.
- Jag and Jas.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
A tandem bike ride forced Angela  to give up control.
You might be better
at driving a car,
but you're not better
at driving a freaking bike! -
KEOGHAN:
Two teams handled the stress
of being in the back
very differently.
- I'm such an idiot.
-Babe, you're not.
Everyone could have
made that mistake.
Just got to keep pedaling.
It doesn't help
that I have the calf muscles
of Woody from Toy Story.
KEOGHAN:
Brothers Jas and Jag set the pace,
narrowly beating brothers
Tucker and Eric.
You are teams
number one and two.
Yeah!
KEOGHAN:
Meanwhile, Jersey brothers Enzo and Jack
couldn't overcome
their hazard...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, oh, bro.
Get out, yo.
Come on, let's go. - Come on.
...and were eliminated
from the race.
Horrible leg,
but we ended strong. - Definitely.
That's it. It is what it is.
KEOGHAN:
Coming up tonight,
travel plans get derailed.
We got off at the wrong station!
KEOGHAN:
And Adam walks the plank.
I-I don't know.
Route Info.
"Travel by train to Prague."
All teams will now
take an overnight train
from the Netherlands
through Germany
to the capital
of the Czech Republic-- Prague.
Regarded as Europe's
most walkable city,
something teams will be doing a
lot of on this leg of the race.
- Let's go. Let's do it.
- All right, let's do this.
All right.
Let's try to find a taxi.
We're brothers,
we're also best friends.
And we're roommates,
we're also business partners.
So literally,
everything that we do,
we do together.
We do together.
We grew up in Omak, Washington.
It's in the middle of nowhere
in Eastern Washington.
JAG:
Growing up, we never had anyone in media
that we could look up to.
For us to be those people
that, you know, like,
younger us's can look up to,
I think that's pretty amazing.
Do you know how to get
to Amsterdam Centraal Station?
Yeah?
Tucker and Eric
are right behind us.
- "Travel to train to Prague..."
- Prague!
"...the capital
of the Czech Republic."
Let's get it. Let's get it.
We're going
to Amsterdam Centraal Station.
- All right, let's get it.
- Yeah, let's do it.
And we know we're trying to go
to Praha Railway Station.
So hopefully,
we're able to find something,
um, that gives us at least
some lead over the other teams.
All right, let's do this.
- Bye. Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much.
TUCKER:
I know we're doing The Amazing Race
and everyone wants first,
but we're playing
withBig Brother players,
so there's a lot of scheming
and working around stuff.
All the teams
seem pretty competitive
right out of the gate.
We lined up pretty quickly
with Jas and Jag.
They know how to play
this game. They know how to win.
Jag has won before
onBig Brother.
So I think that
we just stay tight with them.
- Hi.
- Hi. We are looking to get train tickets to Prague.
We need to buy tickets
to Prague.
I have not been
to Prague before,
but I've worked
in the past with a lot
of musicians from Prague.
We're good millennials,
and we met online. Swiped right.
- The rest was kind of history.
-Yeah.
IZZY:
And we realized that we wanted to do life together.
I'm a professional flutist.
I have no memories
before playing the flute.
PAIGE:
I'm a lighting designer for theater and live events.
We're really hoping
to be underestimated
by the other teams.
We don't look like athletes
because we're not.
IZZY:
We're gamers through and through,
and we would love to exploit
everyone's low expectations
of us.
But we really, really,
really want to win.
I just hear it's beautiful.
So, yeah, I'm really stoked
to finally get to go
and see it and explore.
Getting there earlier
will give us a better head start
- and better buffer of time.
- Yes. To get to the tower.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
I think
the strategy for today is
to just kind of center
our nerves a little bit,
and I think we should be good.
We're in a decent position,
obviously, in the middle,
but our plan is
to get up front today.
That's the one.
That's the one that we'd like.
- In Dresden, yes. Thank you.
- Okay.
Dresden to Prague,
and that's no stops? Come on.
Yeah. Perfect.
We just got the tickets
that we were hoping for
from Amsterdam to Dresden,
a layover in Berlin.
-Yup.
- And then we're going to be spending the night
in Dresden, but then hopping
on a 7:00 a.m. train
from Dresden to Prague.
- Thank you. Perfect.
- Perfect.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Let's go.
ERIC:
We feel pretty confident.
From here on out,
we're, we're coasting.
Coasting in Prague, baby.
- Coasting in Prague.
- Let's get it.
I know that Bohemia is
in the Czech Republic,
like "Bohemian Rhapsody."
I'm two years older,
but we have not spent
more than three weeks together
under the same roof
since I was 12 and she was nine.
When I was 12,
I was accepted
into a boarding school
for students that are gifted.
Graduated from college at 19,
got my master's in three years.
Now I'm in my third year
of med school, and I'm 24.
This race, I'd say, represents
us making up for lost time.
We're hoping placing eighth
will slightly disarm.
So now, at this point, we slowly
want to climb the ladder
and creep up
behind these other teams.
I mean, look,
we got the Express Pass.
So when it comes to actually
getting challenges done, like,
we're solid there.
I feel really confident.
Just curious if everyone's
gonna end up being on this.
Thank you. Love you. Thank you,
Love and appreciate you.
- Say thank you.
- Thank you.
-Thank you!
You're awesome!
Thank you so much!
Are you guys on this train?
What's up?
Yeah, we're getting on this one.
Is this what y'all are doing?
- Yes, that's the one we're on.
- Okay. Yeah.
Yeah, get on in here, boys. - Let's get on.
Right on. Pop a squat.
- Yay.
- Yay. - Yay.
- Oh, my God.
- Breakfast.
I'm sweaty.
Of course
there's friendly competition
between me and Tucker.
Even though
that is my boyfriend,
we know we love each other,
and whatever happens in this,
we're running our own race,
they're running their own race,
and that's fine.
- We're here? Okay.
- Yes, this is it.
Yes, please.
Thank you so much.
Man, we are working some magic.
HANNAH:
Joseph and Adam are gems of human beings.
I have a great relationship
with them
outside of the race,
outside ofBig Brother.
This race is notBig Brother.
But at the same time,
you can't completely run
this race alone.
You're gonna need some help,
so, really thankful
to Joseph and Adam for
kind of giving us that boost,
and all four of us
made that train.
- Group hug!
-Group hug! Yeah!
Good job!
These eight teams
will be traveling together
from Berlin through Dresden
to Prague.
- Oh.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
-I'm so excited! - What is special about Prague?
I love ice hockey
and the men, too.
Okay. A little too old for her. - No.
You would date somebody
over the age of 30?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
She's never had, like,
a full-fledged
relationship boyfriend.
- No?
- Never. And she's 24.
But she's--
yeah, she's very picky.
You make it sound
like it's a bad thing.
It's not a bad thing.
I'm proud of you.
We're going
to Prague, Czech Republic!
- I'm so excited.
- Ah.
I've been there once
for, like, a couple of hours.
Oh. We have a leg up
in the competition.
No, we do not. I was there
for a couple of hours.
- I have a professional.
- I actually got sick,
- so it was not good.
- Oh, uh...
- Um...
- We... I have a professional.
This is international tickets. - TAYLOR: There we go.
We need the tickets
to Praha, Prague.
I think we had some friends
come through.
- Yeah, let's go!
- Amazing. Yes!
Reading comprehension is
both of our not-strong suits,
I guess.
Yeah.
When I was a kid,
I just was always put in, like,
the other classrooms to get help
with reading, reading comp...
As was I.
In my head,
we have a perfect relationship.
MEGAN:
We do have a very specific method
to solve any
of our disagreements.
I'm right, you're wrong, and that's okay.
MATT:
I'm very impulsive when it comes to life in general.
And because of that, I don't
read directions extremely well.
I like
to kind of take my own path.
MEGAN:
I'm more of the follower,
and I like
to stick to the rules.
He's more,
"Let me do what I want."
- We're using our brains.
- Sort of.
Or we're each using a quarter
of our brain. - Quarter.
That's how it's done.
That is how it's done.
What time
does that get us there? - 9:23.
All I heard was that
we're going to get there
at the same time
as the team before us.
-If we catch up...
-If we're caught up
to the rest of the teams,
we have a fighting shot
at getting in the starting pack.
- Ooh-ooh.
These three teams
will be traveling together
through Frankfurt to Prague.
- Nothing else?
- So the earliest is 10:00,
and then it goes to 12:00.
Supposed to arrive at 10:22 a.m.
So then we should go
with the 7:00 p.m.
Okay, we'll do that.
Ah!
Just because
we're last right now
doesn't mean we'll be last
at the end of the leg.
Megan and Matt
will be traveling alone
through Regensburg
to Prague.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Let's figure this out.
We have 28 minutes
until our next train.
What are we doing?
We're going
to Berlin Gesundbrunnen.
Yeah, so we got to get
to platform seven.
We're supposed to go
to platform seven, right, guys?
There's no seven.
We're all lost together.
Guys, we need to hurry up.
I have a funny thing. Berlin...
- Gesundbrunnen.
- Gesundbrunnen?
Berlin.
Did we herd-mentality off
at the wrong Berlin stop?
Did we get off at the wrong station, dude?
Did we get off at the right?
We're in Ber... No, yeah,
we're in Berlin, it says.
We got off at the wrong station.
- Why are you guys running?
- We got off at the wrong stop!
We got off at the wrong station!
- No.
- The train's gone!
The train's gone!
This is not happening.
Okay, we got...
all got off on the wrong stop,
like a bunch of idiots.
This is a nightmare.
We are going to Prague.
-Wow, this is beautiful.
- Yeah, this is... Wow.
- We're gonna get off.
-Thank you.
-Um...
- Yeah, let's do a croissant.
-Oh, look who just
walked in. How long have
you guys been here?
We have an hour
and ten minutes left, so...
- Yeah, same.
- Same.
Have you seen anybody else?
- No.
- No, you guys are
the first faces
we've seen today.
We're going Frankfurt to Prague.
I'm just hoping
we may get there,
and there's still
some teams there
- that we can catch up to.
- Yeah.
JAS:
All the teams got off at the wrong station.
All we saw is "Berlin," but
it's the wrong Berlin station.
We needed to, I think, go
to another-- one more stop.
We're not gonna go
mob mentality.
We're gonna find the tickets.
Okay, this has been a joy.
Do we have a plan?
- Yeah.
- So we're gonna hop back
on the same train and
just get off on the right stop.
Yeah, and then we'll figure out
the next connection
- from there.
- That's what I saw, too.
Oh, geez.
- Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
- Idiot! Idiot!
We were feeling pretty good
about getting to Prague
at the
originally scheduled time,
but just a little bit
of a detour.
Let's get on.
- By the door.
- Yeah, I'm sitting right by the door.
Ay-ay-ay.
One stop away.
Yeah, we lost three teams.
So smart.
STEPHANIE:
We're here with Jag and Jas,
Adam and Joseph.
We don't see any
of the other teams,
so I assume that they already
got on another train.
This gets you there
at 8:00 a.m.
That's not bad.
I don't think we do this solo.
- We ask... Jag? Jas?
- They're upstairs. Let's go ask 'em.
You think the team got
on the earlier train?
- Yeah.
- So they lost the connecting one.
They need new tickets.
What we're gonna do is,
we found tickets straight
to Prague that you can buy here.
That gets you there at 8:00 a.m.
That gets us there
at 8:00 a.m.
So if you guys want
to do that with us,
- that's what we're doing.
- Yes, do it!
Whoo!
We might be up big-time,
boys. Was this a...?
A blessing in disguise?
So, the original tickets we had
would have got us
into Prague at 9:22.
These new tickets get us
into Prague at 8:12 a.m.
We did the group thing,
and it got us here.
Let's stick together till we get
to the next leg, please.
- Can we do that?
- Yeah. We'll do that.
- This is our train, guys.
- I feel like...
This feels like
The Amazing Race. - This is The Amazing Race.
Yeah!
Missing trains! - Yeah!
All right, everyone together?
Seems like this way.
PAIGE:
We lost ourselves
an easier train night,
but I think we have ourselves
back on track
to get that train from Dresden
- to Prague.
-To Prague.
PAIGE:
But we haven't lost ourselves
any time off
of our expected ETA
- since we left Amsterdam.
-Yeah.
We're double-checking to see
if our train is still here.
So, the train was showing up
on here for the past 30 minutes.
-Let's-let's go...
- And it's not showing up here?
We've been waiting out here
for our train.
And we saw that it was delayed
by 18 minutes, then 24 minutes.
And now we're not even seeing it
- on the screen at all.
- On the screen.
Do you guys speak English?
We're waiting for Prague.
What? It's canceled?
Yeah.
Ooh!
- Oh... my gosh.
- Okay.
We had a leg up. Now it looks
like we have a leg down.
The train to take us
to Prague has been canceled,
um, and we are looking up
other options.
The Frankfurt disaster.
I'm not even sure
when we will arrive tomorrow.
All I know is,
I've got comfort knowing
we've got two other teams,
but they're strong teams.
So that's kind of
nerve-racking, too.
There's the train
from Amsterdam to Prague
that has a stop off
in Regensburg.
So that may be
our next best bet.
Some negatives turn
into positives.
Some things that seem bad
at first aren't always so bad.
And maybe the teams that got
the earlier trains got delayed.
Right.
JAS:
We made it.
Woo-hoo!
- Let's go, teams. Let's go.
- Come on, guys.
- Let's get it.
- It's here on the right.
All right, Underground Metro C.
Let's go, let's go.
- Is this it? Is this it?
- C. Metro C.
- Metro C.
-Museum A.
- C to A. Let's go.
-C to A. Let's go.
"Take the metro
and then travel by foot
to the television tower
in Zizkov."
- Let's go, let's go.
- Let's go.
Let's do this.
459?
Yeah, this is it, guys.
EC 459.
- Oh, man. We finally made it.
-Hey, well...
-To Dresden. Dresden.
-Dresden.
And now we're finally
making it...
And now
we're finally on our way
- to Prague.
- ...to Prague.
We're on a train.
- We're on.
- We're on a train to Prague.
- Ground down?
- No, that's not a...
- That's not a thing.
- Okay.
Hopefully, some teams are
too worn out to think straight.
All right.
All right, let's go.
We're here.
Clue box. Clue box.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
We're teams one, two and three! - One, two, three.
Beautiful.
- Roadblock.
- Roadblock. Let's go.
All right, we're team two!
- Oh, Roadblock.
- Roadblock.
"Who wants a breath
of fresh air?" - I do.
- Let me do it.
- Are you sure? It might be a physical thing.
Yeah. Let me do it. I'm fine.
Teams will begin
their adventure
here in Prague
with a bird's-eye view
from the city's
tallest landmark,
Zizkov Television Tower,
famous for the crawling babies
that Czech artist David Cerny
attached to the tower.
This Roadblock requires teams
to walk out
on this narrow plank
hundreds of feet
above the ground
to pick up a clue
dangling precariously below.
Anyone scared of heights
is gonna have
to take a deep breath
before they attempt this one.
- Let's go. That's perfect.
- That's perfect.
That's perfect.
- Oh, my God.
- Um...
It's all right.
It's heights. I can't do it.
- I'll do it. I'll do it.
-Okay.
- Oh, my God, Adam.
-Oh, my gosh. Guys, we did it!
-Let's go!
-Let's keep up the three!
Oh, my God.
What the hell?
What?
- Let's go.
- Oh, I'm so jealous.
- Jas. Nice to meet you.
- Whoo!
Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God.
-What the hell?
I don't like using
the word "afraid," but I think,
looking out here, we're going
to use the word "afraid."
Yeah, chug that orange juice,
baby.
Chugging orange juice.
As a type 1 diabetic,
my pancreas
does not produce insulin.
So that means that I have
to continuously monitor
my blood sugar.
I think this is the perfect
opportunity to show
this isn't gonna be something
that holds me back
but something that's gonna
motivate me and motivate us
to go all the way and win.
My sugar might drop,
but this is a real drop, so
orange juice is needed now.
We've maybe made it to Prague.
We can see the Zizkov
Television Tower from the train.
- There it is. There it is.
It looks taller
than it did on the map.
So everything is clear?
Yes, everything's clear.
We're good to go. - All right.
No nervousness, okay? - Okay.
You got this.
All right.
You can go on the platform.
Yes, sir.
Wow.
This is beautiful.
Oh, my God.
This is whyThe Amazing Race is
such a unique experience,
because no one else gets
to experience such thing.
This is 255 feet for sure.
Good luck.
I should have let you do this.
You can step
on the platform now.
Now stay with me here, please.
Come on, Jasu. Let's do this.
- You're ready to go.
- Ready to go?
Oh, my God.
Let's go!
- Oh.
- Jasu, you got it.
You got it.
Ooh!
Come on, come on, come on.
Red one first.
Wow. There's a cemetery
right below me,
so I guess that's fitting
if I fall off.
Oh, my gosh!
It's up to you. You can go.
I-I don't know.
You got it. Don't overthink it, Adam.
Don't get in your head.
I wish I could take his spot.
I know
he's terrified of heights.
You're clear and good to go.
So proud of you, Steph.
-Ah.
- You can do it, sissy.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Adam, you're perfectly fine.
ADAM:
I thought, "Oh, my God."
There was no way
I was doing this.
Walk forward.
I know
you're fighting a fear now.
Just don't get in your head.
There you go.
Step by step. That's it.
Okay, coming up.
I don't know if I can.
Wow. Look at that.
Okay.
- Just like that.
- And done!
Like cake, like cake.
- You crushed that.
- Hey, come on.
Yo, that was gorgeous.
You're killing it, buddy.
Yay!
Good job, sissy.
That's my sister.
That's my big sis.
- Route Info.
This is Prague's
most famous landmark--
the Charles Bridge--
with more statues than
any other bridge in the world.
Teams must figure out
that their next clue
is on the east side
of the bridge,
next to a statue
of the bridge's namesake
Emperor Charles IV.
"Take the underground metro
and then proceed on foot."
Okay, let's go.
Slow and steady.
Good job, sissy! Yay!
Good job, good job.
We'll see you down there.
Okay, bye, guys.
That's my girl. That's my... -
- That's my sister.
- Whoo!
Yup.
There we go.
Oh, my God.
There's that clue, baby!
I am so proud of you.
Let's go!
I'm coming.
Okay. Let's go.
I'm in Prague... on a building.
Oh, my God, get me off.
- Whoo!
-Baby!
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's go, baby!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I did it.
You did. That was so ....
I think
this might be our train.
We have not seen any
other team since the last leg.
MEGAN:
I saw Kyland and Taylor and then Alex and Kat.
And then I see Lexi and Angela,
and I'm like,
"Oh, my God,
there's three teams right now
on the same exact train as us."
There's not one team.
There's three here.
MATT:
That was the moment
we found hope again.
Three blocks? We got directions.
You guys start jogging.
-We're slow. Let us...
- Yes. Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
- You guys start jogging.
The boys have our back,
'cause they know
that we can't keep up with them.
Nat hasn't been
on Big Brotherfor years.
I've never been
on a TV show before,
so we're just like
sitting ducks in a way.
NATALIE:
This is the season
where the win is going
to be a big win
because this is
the most competitive people.
Three winners ofBig Brother?
Are you kidding me?
So it's really nice knowing
that we can trust Jas and Jag
and also Joseph and Adam.
- Hurry up. Come on. Come on.
- Hey, we have directions.
- Run!
- Run! Run! - You guys waited.
Ah!
Let's go.
Come on, baby.
Pulan, I'm right behind you.
Okay.
Good job.
We need to get
to the Zizkov Television Tower.
Dad!
Hannah and Simone
didn't make it?
are somewhere else.
Did you see them?
I wonder if that's it.
This? The swirly here?
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
Hi. Hello, hello.
Metro.
- Metro?
- Yeah...
- Hlavní Nádrazí.
- Hlavní?
- Yes.
- This is Central Station.
- And this is metro inside.
- Wait. Hlavní Nádrazí is inside?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Go, go, go, go!
-So now we're headed?
-Karluv Most.
-It's a bridge.
- Yeah, it's a bridge.
There? See it?
- Oh, we see it!
- Spotted! Spotted!
-Come on, Joseph!
-They found it.
I see a clue.
Let's go.
Detour.
Prague is world-famous
for its pubs,
and a hot favorite is U Fleku,
that has been serving
and toasting patrons
for more than 500 years.
This Detour requires teams
to study the 11 village crests
on this tapestry,
then search for them
in Knights' Hall
on the back
of the dining chairs.
The names
of each village are displayed
on the front of each chair,
which teams will need
to commit to memory
and then make their way
to the back of Knights' Hall,
where they must recite
the names of the villages
as a historian points
to each village crest.
Czech glass, or as it's commonly
known, Bohemian glass,
is internationally recognized
for its distinctive designs,
quality, craftsmanship
and beauty.
This Detour requires teams
to pick up 48
of these affordable
national treasures
and then deliver them
to three vendors.
Once they've collected stamps
from all of them, they can
hand them over for a clue.
I think we're gonna do
Handle with Care.
We should all do this.
"Remember the Chair or Handle with Care."
Jag, Jas,
what are you guys thinking?
We're thinking
Handle with Care.
How good's
your memory right now?
Natalie and Stephanie, we're
gonna go with Handle with Care.
We're gonna go
with Handle with Care.
- Let's go. Yeah.
- We're gonna do it.
- Let's go.
-Now, this is
- The Amazing Race,baby!
- Dude, look at that view!
Dude, this is gorgeous!
- There it is. There it is.
- There it is.
Take the next number-- four.
Yeah, so those guys
made it somehow.
"Who wants a breath
of fresh air?" - Me.
- You got it, Tuck.
- Me. A breath of fresh air.
"Walk a plank
250 feet above the ground
and receive your next clue
from a dangling rope"?
- Let's go.
- Shut up.
Oh, right there? Done.
Go get it, baby.
"Who wants a breath
of fresh air?"
- You?
- Uh, I'll do it, yeah.
I want a breath of fresh air.
She wants a breath of fresh air.
I love her so much.
- You do.
- I do.
- You want a breath of fresh air.
- I want a breath of fresh air.
Ooh, let's go.
Look at this view.
I know. This is sick.
No fear, ready to rock.
Oh, God, this is iconic.
-Is it here?
- It's right here.
There's a sign.
Right here, guys.
Here. Kavárna.
Yeah, this is it.
Don't second-guess us.
Come on.
Hi. How's it going?
Oh, this is where
we have to travel.
"Choose two crates to carry your goblets.
"When you think you have
collected all the goblets,
deliver them to locations
on your order forms."
Okay, let's go.
There's very specific orders
on what number
of goblets
and what color they want.
So we're, right now,
filling all of those up.
There's 24 slots in each.
To keep this organized, all--
Adam, not like that.
I got it.
Whoo-ee!
That's gonna be crazy.
- Yeah, you got this, Tuck.
- Kill it.
There's just a graveyard
right down there.
It's like,
"All right, well, you know,
"if something goes wrong,
at least
I'll land in the right place."
You're ready to go.
Let's do it.
Let's go, Tucker!
Ooh.
You got it, Tuck.
Damn it!
He's crushing it right now.
He made it over there.
No hesitation.
Maybe it's the hard part.
He's got some great balance.
And he's back
on the tower already, baby!
- Let's go.
-Let's go!
Mom's gonna have the willies!
All right. "Make your way
to Krizovnické Námestí
to find your next clue."
You got this, Dad.
Okay.
Being a firefighter,
you can't be afraid of heights.
I've been a firefighter
for the past 31 years.
CHELSIE:
Growing up with a dad who's a firefighter,
it was fun
because we got to brag,
"Our dad's a firefighter.
Oh, my gosh."
But on the other hand...
...he would come...
He would see
a lot of things on the job.
He was overly protective.
We haven't had a real
Christmas tree since 1996.
Ready.
Nice.
Nice and steady.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Hi.
- Hi. - How you doing?
Good job, Dad.
We're in a good spot.
Just take your time.
- Oh, oh, oh.
- You call this a Roadblock?
- Let's go.
- What?
This is not a block.
This is just a road, baby.
- Right.
- Thomas, do you do this a lot?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
And so far, so good?
You're still alive?
- Of course.
- Yeah. Okay, great.
"Who wants a breath
of fresh air?"
- I'll do it.
- You got it.
So, three red, two blue,
three yellow.
Nat, what page are you doing?
Kafe & Hrnky.
This is purple,
so we need a blue.
- Are you sure this is purple?
- What else is purple?
Oh, my God, I missed so many.
- Nat, I need you to focus.
- I am.
- Okay...
- We're gonna start getting directions.
Let's get outside.
We counted everything,
double-checked.
And we're out of there before
the other two teams
that we're working with.
Oh, my gosh.
Come on.
Does someone speak English here?
Oh, my God.
- Okay.
- Can we use your phone for directions?
We need
three different locations.
So let's start with this one.
There were
three different locations,
so we wanted to make sure that
the three locations, we went
in order, most efficient route.
- A...
- It's all on the same street.
- Let's go. Let's go. Okay.
- Let's go. Okay.
Okay, perfect.
We're ready to go.
- Whoo!
- Careful! Careful! -
Yay!
- Good to go.
-You got this, Pulan.
Slow and steady.
You got this.
I'm doing it.
Okay.
Okay, so now get the directions
- from here to the next...
- We're here.
To number two.
- Hey, guys, are you...?
- That's Kafe Hrnky.
Where'd Jag and Jas go?
They already left.
We got to go. - They left.
Kafe "Henry," 224/25.
- Two-two...
- Kafe "Henry" right there.
Good job.
Excuse me.
- Hello.
- We have a delivery for you.
- Of goblets.
Hopefully have the right colors.
We double-checked
before we left.
Beautiful.
Five purple. Correct.
- Yay.
- Awesome. Thank you.
- Can we get a stamp, please?
- Of course.
Thank you.
-Next, Neruda Café.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Slow and steady. You got this.
I can do this.
I got this.
You did so good.
- That was excellent.
- That was fun. No sweat.
She's doing so good.
She's almost done.
Oh, I'm so proud of her.
Yay!
Wow. I didn't let out
any screams.
You're ready to go.
Simone, please, no talking.
- Excuse us.
- Yeah. What's it called?
Uh, Café Neruda.
Oh, there we are.
- Hi.
- We have something for you. - Okay.
We have a special delivery
of colorful goblets. - Thank you.
These are for you to count.
All of them out.
And there you go,
and then two of these.
-Perfect.
-Perfect. Thank you.
And thank you for the stamp.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Thank you so much.
-Whoo!
-Right there.
Okay, let's go.
Neruda Café.
Oh, here it is.
- Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
We love you.
Yes, let's go!
Oh, it's so good to see you
with all these...
We love Czech Republic.
Thank you for having us. Whoo!
We're ready. We're ready.
No, are we at the wrong place?
Oh, we're not here.
It's not here. - No. Come on, guys.
Did he just pull us
in here to party?
I cannot believe that guy
just pulled us in there.
"Ah, come on, come in."
And we just walked in.
You said
you wanted a heights challenge.
Can't get higher than 255 feet.
- Good job.
- Thank you. Thank you, thank you.
- That was amazing.
- She's a prima ballerina.
-Hello.
- Hi.
- How's it going?
- Hi, guys.
- We have something for you.
- We have a special delivery.
- Do you have the sheet?
- Yes, we do.
- Great.
- Two reds, a blue.
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
Two yellows, three greens.
- Yeah.
- And two purples.
- Okay.
-Yeah!
Thank you so much.
We go right back
to where we came.
We might have to get directions.
It's literally on this road.
Are you sure?
Wait. There's Jag and Jas.
- Jag! Jas!
-Jag!
I see them over there.
Have you delivered any?
We haven't delivered
the first one yet.
And you skipped one
right across the street.
Turn left. The sign is
kind of hard to see.
- You can't tell what it says.
-We passed the first?
Neruda, go in here.
You don't leave this street.
All right, good luck, guys.
-Hello, hello.
- Hi.
-Hello!
-Hello! - JOSEPH: Hello, hello.
It's so good to see you.
We found one, thank God.
Slow and steady.
- Three green?
- Three green.
Gentle, sissy.
-Thank you.
- Yes, hello. Welcome.
- Four red.
Four yellow, three green,
six purple.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's go, guys.
Everybody burn those butts.
All right.
We've delivered
all your goblets.
And we got 'em all stamped.
There you go.
- Oh, thank God!
- Oh, let's go.
"Travel on foot
to the Josef Mánes statue
outside the Rudolfinum
to find your next clue."
- Okay, perfect. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Here's one purple, one orange.
-Thank you so much.
-Perfect. Yay!
Thank you.
Thank you. Two down, one to go.
- We made it!
- Okay, baby, let's go.
We made it to Prague!
TAYLOR:
We arrive in Prague with three other teams.
We told everyone
that we were moving as a unit
to navigate
to the Zizkov Television Tower.
One stop red,
transfer, three stops green.
But just horror shot
through my veins after realizing
this could be
the final four teams,
and one of us is likely
to be eliminated.
And we were just immediately
back fighting for our lives.
Fingers crossed
that there's a ton of clues
left over there and we're...
- not in the last group.
- One of the first teams.
All right, good luck,
squad. Let's get it.
Let's move.
Kyland and Taylor,
y'all are killing it right now.
Thank you. Excuse us.
You got it.
Oh, my gosh.
- What's the name of the shop?
- Kafe & Hrnky.
Oh, guys, it's in here. - ADAM: Yeah.
Let's start counting
our goblets.
Let's go, guys.
Three red, two blue,
three yellow,
two green, five purple.
Whoo! You are up, ladies.
Two blue, three yellow,
two green, five purple.
And...
Yes! Let's go, sissy!
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
Quick, quick, quick.
Speed it up. Come on, guys.
We're on The Amazing Race,
not on The Amazing Turtle.
JAS:
The no sleep
is wearing on me.
- Route Info.
- Route info.
"Race to... on your Pit Stop."
Let's go!
Many of the world's
greatest composers,
including Tchaikovsky,
have performed right here
at Zofín Palace.
It continues to host concerts,
balls, and galas
and today
will roll out the red carpet
for an Amazing RacePit Stop.
The last team to check in here
will be eliminated.
- Okay.
- Okay, we've got to get some directions.
- Zofín Palace.
- Let's go.
-Oh, my God.
- Hi.
My vendor.
Here you go, kind sir.
- Joseph, you have all three?
- All three, baby.
Please.
Yes!
We love you!
My good sir.
- Yay!
- Whoo!
"Travel on foot to the
Josef Mánes statue and..."
"...find your next clue."
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
-Right.
-Right here.
Ninth.
I'm doing the Roadblock.
"Who wants a...
a breath of fresh air?" - Me. Me.
"Who wants a breath
of fresh air?"
- You do.
- Okay. I'll do it.
Mom, look what
I'm seeing up there.
This isn't a trick.
- You do it.
- Okay.
MAN:
So, right here,
- facing my direction.
- Facing you.
Cool.
Now we will attach first rope.
Hey, what's up, everybody?
-Hey, what's up?
- Oh, God.
This is crazy.
- I'll be safe.
- Love you.
Adam, come on.
Statue should be there.
That's it. Jog.
I see a clue box.
Clue box.
- Come on, Adam.
- All right, let's go.
"Race on foot
to your next Pit Stop inside...
to find Phil on the mat."
- Oh! Guys, we got to go.
-Okay. Zofín Palace.
JAS:
Let's go.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
- Whoo!
- All right. Good job.
Welcome to Prague.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. - Thank you. We love it.
Do you recognize this gentleman?
Uh, maybe a composer?
- He's Dvorák.
-Dvorák.
- We were gonna guess that next.
- Ah. On the tip of my tongue.
And you are team number one.
Let's go! Let's go!
And I do have
some great news for you.
As the winners
of this leg of the race,
you have won OneKeyCash
from Expedia,
which you could use towards
a trip for two... to Sri Lanka.
- Oh!
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
Expedia has designed a nine-day guided tour
around Sri Lanka
with major attractions,
featuring a Sigiriya rock climb,
a scenic train ride in Ella,
a wildlife safari
in Yala National Park,
and...
a cultural dance show in Kandy.
- Whoa! That's so cool.
- That's so cool.
So if you were to pick teams
that you feel like
you were going to be racing with
later in the race,
who do you think
those teams are gonna be? - JAS: Honestly,
the other two teams
that were with us... - Helped a ton.
...Joseph and Adam and Natalie
and Stephanie-- helped a ton.
We were working together as, like, a trio.
And they're extremely smart.
So far, that's who
we feel good about.
- This was it right here.
- That was the dome, too.
But you just clicked
on the area.
- No.
- And there was a picture of something in the area.
- Oh, there's a clue box.
- I've been telling you.
Route Info.
"Race on foot
to your next Pit Stop..."
Oh, dude, let's go.
"...inside Zofín Palace
and find Phil on the mat."
Pit Stop? Are you kidding me?
Wait, we're already
at the theater?
-Dude.
- Zofín.
I can't believe
it's the Pit Stop, bro.
I was expecting, like,
two, three more challenges.
I was expecting
to go until, like, 6:00 p.m.
Yeah. Man.
Thank you, Phil. Thank you.
- Thank you, Amazing Race.
- Amazing Race.
Oh, giving us a little bit
of a breather.
-Oh, yeah, these stairs.
-Oh, this is the palace.
Phil!
Nat, run!
- Oh... my... God.
- Oh.
All right, Joseph and Adam,
I'm pleased to tell you
that you are team number two.
Natalie and Stephanie,
that would make you
team number three.
- You're on the podium.
- Yes.
Oh, my God, baby,
let's go.
Not the cemetery below me.
Geez, guys.
Ooh. This is a lot harder
than I was expecting.
Okay. Ooh!
Holy moly.
No reason to rush.
Okay.
Whoa. All right.
I'm, like, questioning
all my balance right now.
I feel like...
Yeah, you know what?
- Let's just take that.
-Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
All right.
This is actually way scarier
when I got up here.
If you need to,
you will just shout "Help."
You got it!
- I can't believe I'm doing this!
-You got it.
All right, I'm done.
- Oh, my God.
-Thank you.
Are you kidding me?
"Make your way
to Krizovnické Námestí
to find your next clue."
- Let's go.
- Yeah, take those off. Let's roll.
- All right, let's go.
- Let's go.
- All right.
This is scarier than it looks. - MEGAN: It's okay.
I just need a second.
I just know
that we're in last right now.
You're hooked up.
And I feel, like,
a lot of pressure.
Don't feel the pressure.
You've got this. - Okay.
The second I move,
I start shaking.
Sorry. I'm sweating now, Megan.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
Dude, I'm gonna cry.
Okay.
Okay. Ooh.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-Very good.
Very good, my dear.
Oh, my God.
You got it.
You've got it. Just go. You got it.
Okay.
Oh.
There you go!
It's okay.
I'm right here.
You're safe.
Just keep going.
It's fine.
Little by little.
- Megan, this is so scary.
- Little by little.
There you go.
Just take baby steps.
This is not real.
I don't think
I've ever felt, like,
anxiety like this in my life.
Oh, my God, my legs are,
like, shaking right now.
I can't look. I can't look.
Mom, look at me.
I'm so proud of you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- That was so close.
- Look at what you freaking just did!
Yes!
Great work!
- I'm so proud of you!
- Thank you. Keep going.
I need
to hear your voice right now.
Oh, my gosh. Look at you go!
Okay, let's just get out of here
with that so far, okay?
Good job!
Nice. Nice. Nice.
Oh, my God. I'm so proud of you.
I'm so proud of you.
That was tough.
"Make your way
to the Krizovnické Námastí
to find your next clue."
That's it. Zofín Palace, baby.
Hey. Whoo!
Tucker and Eric, you're
the fourth team to arrive.
- Let's go, baby!
- Let's go. That's what we thought. Ah!
However, you have not
completed the Detour.
So you need to go back out
onto the race course,
complete the Detour
before I can check you in.
Figure it out. Let's go.
Turns out the Pit Stop
was too good to be true.
So we're going
to go find this Detour, baby.
- Aw, man.
- Damn!
-This is it.
-Yeah.
Okay, do we see it?
-There's a clue box!
-Where?
Right there to the right.
Let's go.
Love that.
- Detour.
"Remember the Chair
or Handle with Care."
If we do this together...
- You guys.
- We can do it together.
-Together?
- I do think
- more brains...
-Will help it.
We're going
to do Remember the Chair.
We're gonna choose
Remember the Chair. - Remember the Chair.
Detour. "Remember the Chair
or Handle with Care."
Hey, guys, what are you doing?
Remember the Chair.
We might as well stay close
to them and do the Chair.
Over there.
Hi, guys.
- What? Let it go.
- Hell yes.
- Okay. We got to move.
- We got to move.
Detour.
Time for a little jog, guys.
We got to go.
All right, let's take
Remember the Chair. - I don't care at all.
- All right.
- RUBINA: We just saw Tucker and Eric
at the clue box,
but they were before us
at the tower,
so guess what.
Okay. Love you.
Sorry, Tucker,
if you're seeing this.
Good job, babe.
But we're doing a gooder job.
We should have known by
Phil's face when we walked in.
No smile.
No eyebrow up.
Dang.
Detour. "Remember the Chair
or Handle with Care."
- Remember the Chair.
- Always.
Always. We're really good
when it comes to memory stuff.
-I'm dying.
-This is really hard.
U Fleku. This is it.
This is it.
Good job, everyone.
-Hello.
Oh, here. Right here.
We have to find these
crests and learn the names.
Eight, nine, ten, 11.
Let's get a rhythm
of what we're supposed to do.
- Yeah, I know. Yeah.
- Yeah.
My God.
Oh, man.
Okay, let's do it.
Sorry.
Baby, I found the sardines.
- So now what do we do?
- Awesome.
Uh, excuse me.
Can I ask you a question?
How do you say this?
- "Ash."
- "Ash." - "Ash."
"Ash. Ash."
IZZY:
People were sitting in chairs
that had crests in the back,
so we had to learn
how to pronounce the names
of these towns
and pair them
with the matching crests.
And to do that, it was a little
bit like needle in the haystack,
finding the crests
and then asking
these awesome Czech people
trying to enjoy their lunch
how to pronounce the names
and learning them.
-How do I say this?
-Yeah, like "Lito Mish-la."
- "Little Mish-la."
- "Mish-la."
That's me. Little Mish-la.
Yeah. I'm so sorry. So sorry.
KRISTINE:
It was very
instantly chaotic.
Pulan? Look for yours.
I'm gonna keep going.
- Do you hear me? Hello?
-Yeah. Yes!
KRISTINE:
The six of us in the room
running through the chairs
all at the same time,
learning the pronunciation,
so we're hearing
everybody's conversation.
"Brr-no. Brr-no."
It was just chaos.
"Brr-no, Rye-rad, Little..."
All righty.
All right, we're here.
- I need to go find two flowers.
- "Brr-no..."
CHELSIE:
It was absolutely chaotic.
And then
Eric and Tucker show up.
I was with Tucker
all summer for Big Brother.
The guy has a great memory.
So when he walked in there,
I was like,
"Oh, Lord, here we go."
How do you pronounce
this one again?
- "Beel-chit-say."
- "Beel-chit-say"?
Yes.
It's a tough one.
Repetition is key.
Repetition is key. - Yeah.
- "Freedland."
- "Sha-bon."
- "Ho-mu-tov."
- Slow and steady.
We want to just do it right
the first time.
Okay, let's do it.
You got this.
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- Yes. Go on... yes, you got it.
- Let's try it.
- Okay, let's try it.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hi. - Hello, welcome.
It's in different
order, but that's okay. - Okay.
"Vish-kov."
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Hold on.
"Beel-chit-say."
"Ho-mu-tov."
"Little Mish-la."
"Rye-rad."
"Ash."
Um... "Freedland."
"Tre-bon-ye."
"Oon-ee-tov."
"Bo-kov."
"Bo-ya-nov."
I'm sorry. Incorrect.
-Oh!
-Let's look again.
- We got this.
- It's okay.
- "Se-bon-ye. Se-bon-ye."
-Okay.
-"Se-bon-ye."
-Okay. "Se-bon-ye."
I think we're ready.
Do we...?
I got it. I'm good.
- You got this.
- I had it.
It's okay.
Don't be hard on yourself.
"Hog-bov."
Ah. I don't remember this one,
dude.
"Bo-ya-nov"?
I'm sorry. Incorrect.
Get back!
"Boy-chut"?
And "Bo-ya-chov."
Incorrect.
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Okay.
- That's okay. Don't worry. Don't get frustrated.
We just have to keep trying.
- Oh, clue!
- Yes!
"Remember the Chair
- or Handle with Care."
- "...or Handle with Care."
- Handle with Care.
- All right, we'll Handle with Care.
Um...
"Bo-kov."
"Bo-ya-nov."
Incorrect.
Really? Okay. Thank you.
"Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Sorry. Incorrect.
- Ugh.
- Hi, sir.
- Hello again. - Hi.
- We're back.
- We're back. - Okay. Okay.
"Bish-kov."
"Beel-chit-say."
"Ho-mu-tov."
"Sech."
"Rye... Rye-rad."
"Ash."
"Freedland."
"Tre-bon."
"Brr-no."
"Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
Oh! Oh, my God! Oh, my gosh!
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, sir.
- Mmm.
- Aw. Me, too. Yay!
Route Info.
Okay. "Travel on foot
to the Josef Mánes statue."
Remember, we act like
we're in last place. - Yes.
- Hello!
-How's it going?
-Hooray.
"Ask the shopkeeper
for three order forms."
- Can we have three order forms?
- Can we have the order forms, please?
Thank you.
This is one, two, three. - Thank you.
Goblets. Three red,
two blue, three yellow,
two green, five purple.
Here's two green.
- Handle with care.
-Careful, please.
Yes, sir. Sorry about that.
"Bear-no."
"Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- Thank you, sir.
- "Rye-rad."
- "Rye-rad." - TUCKER: Let's go!
-Oh, they got it.
- Don't worry about them.
- I'm not.
Come on, baby! You guys got this.
- Good job."
- "Sha-bon."
-Good job.
-Keep hammering.
At least we know where to go.
Yeah. Exactly where we were.
-This is amazing.
-Got it.
Oh. Detour. "Remember the Chair
or Handle with Care."
I think
we're better at remembering.
- Let's go.
- Famous last words.
We're gonna do the Chair.
- Two green?
- Two green.
- Three purple?
- Three purple. Two...
- One orange.
- That's one. Yes.
Okay, perfect. And then we need
- to go to these places.
- Yes.
- Ooh.
- Okay, so we need to find directions.
"Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
Incorrect.
We have
to try something different
because we can't keep
trying the same thing.
- That one's mine, right?
- Uh-huh.
Okay. "Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
Perfect.
- Go!
- Correct.
- Thank you so much.
We are sorry for what we did
to your language.
It's beautiful.
These are beautiful.
-One and done.
-Yeah.
We slayed that.
"Little Mish-la."
I know this.
The crests are correct.
I think the crests are correct, too.
"Bear... Bear-no."
"Bo-kov."
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
- Amazing.
Can I hug you? Yes.
-Pulan, they got it.
-Stop it. Stop it.
-Everybody left.
-Don't...
- Hey, we're still ahead.
- I know. I know.
Release the frustration,
because we're just trying
to figure it out.
Well, well, well.
Thank you. Thank you.
Touched it.
We already got it.
Yeah, we're back.
Okay, let's go.
We got it.
There you go.
Oh, my God. We're here.
- Detour.
Of course it is.
We're going
to do Remember the Chair.
We're going to do
Remember the Chair.
Remembering the Chair.
- We're still in this.
- It's this one.
-Yeah?
-I mixed it up.
- You mixed it up? That's okay.
- Yes. What's this?
"Brr-no. Brr-no."
- "Brr-no."
- "Brr-no." Yes.
"Brr-no."
- Okay, I got it.
- You got it?
- Yes, let's try it again.
- Let's try again.
"Brr-no."
"Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
Incorrect.
Don't get... It's okay.
Six tries later,
we were still getting it wrong.
KRISTINE:
Getting it wrong.
You're like, "Why can't we get
this and everyone else can?"
I feel like I'm saying it
exactly how they're saying it.
Right, so then if you feel
like you're saying it right,
there's something else.
"Bo-ya-nov."
"Little Mish-la."
Take it easy, take a breath.
I know. I'm just trying to...
I know.
I just need quiet right now.
I can get frustrated
really easily.
It was just a high-stress
situation.
Sorry. Incorrect.
Incorrect.
Okay.
Let's try it. Let's practice.
- I know.
-What is it?
This one. I don't have the gold one.
It was gold.
- This one.
- Oh, my God.
-"Sech." "Sech."
- "Sech"? "Sech"?
KRISTINE:
We were thinking it was a pronunciation,
but in reality
we were choosing...
RUBINA:
The wrong crest.
So there were similar ones,
obviously. Ha!
Attention to detail
in this Amazing Race?
That's new. No.
"Sech."
- Do you know?
- Yeah. "Sech."
"Rye-rad."
"Ash."
"Freedland."
"Sha-bon-ye."
"Bur-no."
"Bo-hoff."
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Perfect.
- Yeah. I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- So hard.
- It's okay.
- I'm really sorry.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you. - Thank you so much.
-Kafe!
-Yes!
All right. Go on in.
- Hello!
- Hi.
- Hi. We have a delivery for you.
- For you.
We have three red,
two blue. Thank you.
Three yellow.
Two green and five purple.
Correct.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
I love your hair.
- Amazing. Thank you.
- Thank you.
We had to double back,
we found the right clue.
- Yup.
- We did the Detour.
Tucker and Eric,
I'm pleased to tell you
that you are now
team number four.
- Let's go!
- We stayed in fourth place!
- Let's go, baby.
Now, see,
the ice cream is way better.
We got ice cream
and fridge magnets
to celebrate what we think
is maintaining our fourth place,
despite our blunders
from earlier.
Kept the same place.
-All right.
-Okay.
I'll take... I'll take the red
and make it easy...
- yellow and green.
- Okay.
Let's just start with the blue,
and then we can see from there,
'cause we might have to change.
- All right.
- So, fish.
Here, fishy. Fish?
May I ask you
how to pronounce this?
- "Ash."
So, "Ash, Ash, Ash," fish.
We can do it.
This is gonna be easy.
Hannah and Simone,
I'm pleased to tell you
that you are team number five.
Here we go. Two green,
one orange, two red,
two yellow, three purple, one...
- Yes? Yes. Yes!
- Thank you!
All right, babe.
- Thank you so much.
- You, too.
Back where we came, remember?
Yup. Exactly.
Hey, Joseph.
There's still a bunch left.
- "Find Phil on the mat."
- Fine, let's go to the mat!
Our greeter is playing the role
of a famous Czech composer.
Is it Dvorák?
- Oh, my God.
- Very good.
Yes!
Nice to meet you, Antonín.
- "Bo-hoff." "Bo-hoff."
- "Bo-hoff."
Come on. I think other teams
are right behind us.
Oh, wow.
- Okay.
- Um, so...
Dude, I don't know...
"Freedland." "Tay-bon."
Kat, can you give us a clue
on where we go?
I... I'm memorizing really hard.
I understand.
Hello, sir. How's it going?
We got your three stamps.
- Ooh. Yes! Thank you.
- Thank you.
DVORÁK:
Welcome to Prague.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, sir.
Jack and Chelsie,
I'm pleased to tell you
that you are team number seven.
- Seven.
- Seven. All right!
- Aren't you glad to see us?
- So glad to see you.
- Oh.
Kristine and Rubina,
I'm pleased to tell you
that you are team number eight.
- Yes, we'll take it.
- Yes... It's okay. It's okay.
We knew it, we knew it,
and we're okay.
"Freedland." "Dose-a-bo-ya."
- "Ho-ma-dov."
- Ugh. Ugh.
"But-kov."
No, no, no. No "T."
Lexi, see if you can get this.
- "Bo-hoff."
- Yeah? Yeah?
- Yes. Very good. - "Bo-hoff."
- You're doing good.
- I know. I don't know what's happening.
- Yeah. Let's go. Let's go.
- Hell yeah.
Thank you, guys.
You got it.
"Bo-ya-nov."
Gosh, thank you. Oh, my.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you.
- Ah.
- ♪ Ah!♪
Oh, my gosh.
I have mine, too.
Did you guys do it?
You got this.
Just everyone talk
to themselves for now.
LEXI:
Kat and Alex had left.
It was very stressful.
We knew we were
the last two teams there.
I'm sorry. Incorrect.
Incorrect.
- Incorrect. I'm sorry.
- What?!
Incorrect.
- Incorrect. I'm sorry.
- No!
It was a very,
very tense situation.
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Incorrect. Sorry.
- Oh. - Oh.
This is, like, mentally
breaking me right now.
If you think
you have what it takes
to win The Amazing Race,
then go to cbs.com/casting
and apply now.
The world is waiting for you.
- Get in focus.
- It's okay.
It's okay. It's silly. It's so silly.
- Damn it. It's so silly.
- We don't know the language.
We haven't slept in 48 hours.
- We got this.
-Okay.
Megan, I have been
messing this up drastically.
There it is.
"Race on foot to your next
Pit Stop inside Zofín Palace.
- Find Phil on the mat."
- Yes! Oh.
"Bo-ya-nov."
It's an honor. Thank you.
"Vish-kov."
"Beel-chit-say."
MATT:
This was yet another instance
where Angela and Lexi
finished before us.
In that moment
it was make-or-break.
"Bo-ya-nov."
- Correct.
- Okay.
We got it.
We got it. All right. - Thank you.
It says "statue
outside of the..." - We got it.
- Yay!
- Yes!
- We did it, you guys.
- And, guys,
if it's the Phil thing,
we all just got to run.
We did it!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Josef Mánes.
-Josef.
-Oh, my God.
"Find Phil on the mat."
Kyland and Taylor,
I'm pleased to tell you
that you are team number nine.
All right.
You are team
number ten. Congratulations.
Oh, my gosh.
"Race on foot to your next
Pit Stop inside Zofín Palace
and find Phil on the mat."
So where is Zofín Palace?
Zofín Palace.
Can we go with them?
It's... No.
It's not over till it's over.
We got to go. I can't be loyal anymore.
I'm fighting for a million
dollars for the family.
-Yes.
- Not for Angela and Lexi.
We're not done. We're not done.
We're not done.
I thought it'd be on our right.
We can ask
maybe one more person. - Right.
We don't know what's gonna happen.
All we can hope right now is
that they couldn't
find this place.
No matter what happens,
we're trying our best.
Trying our best.
-Is that it?
-It is, it is.
This has to be Zofín Palace.
Okay, this is it, Megan.
One more push up these steps.
I want to run to him, but I can't.
Phil, I'm coming for you.
Hey.
- Oh, Phil.
-Wow.
Oh, God, is it good to see you.
I'm so happy to see you.
Megan and Matt,
I am pleased to tell you
that you are not
the last team to arrive.
-Let's go.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
You are team number 11.
- Yup.
- That's our lucky number, Phil.
That's our lucky number.
Give it all you got.
Come on. Come on.
- Good job. Good job.
-You too.
Thank you.
Angela and Lexi,
unfortunately, you are
the last team to arrive,
and I'm sorry to tell you
you have been eliminated
from the race.
- It's okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
I'm really proud of her.
I'm beyond proud of my mom.
You know, she's 51 years old.
She's up against 20,
30-year-olds on this race,
and you're still keeping up
pretty good.
ANGELA:
You know, I'm a mom, and I kind of
helicopter parent
a little too much.
She's impressed me,
and I think moving forward,
it's giving me
a newfound respect for my girl,
and I think
she does for me, too.
LEXI:
I do.
So you're gonna take
the AirTag out of my car?
No, I still need
to know where you are.
- I'm taking it out of my car.
- You're hundreds of miles away.
- She can trust me now.
- She's hundreds of miles away.
She's hundreds of miles away.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Next time on
The Amazing Race...
When the Driver's Seat
returns...
Let's strategize.
KEOGHAN:
...the plotting begins...
Target's on our back.
- That works with us, yeah.
- We're trying
to keep our hands clean.
KEOGHAN:
...and shakes up the race.
Aah!
Once he start spiraling,
it's over.
My Lord.
I'm so over this.